<?xml version="1.0" charset="UTF-8" ?>
<setting>
<serverlink>rtmp://localhost:1935</serverlink>
<serverlink2>rtmp://localhost:1935</serverlink2>
<serverlink3>rtmp://locahost:1935</serverlink3>

<webcodes>shadow,Lumens,Grasshop</webcodes>
<bonusdate>14-5-2007,31-12-2009,31-12-2009</bonusdate>

<mainvolume>1</mainvolume>
<infopanel>FadeToStar*hunter*Winning battles is the key to moving up levels|
FadeToBlue*mantis*My champion in the swamp will defeat you!|
WhipeUp*corona*Find the mini-game in the mountains to help Igneous|
TweenToWhite*sparkle*Play the Invasion mini-game in the village to help Corona|
FadeToStar*teacher*Customize your decks to use against different opponents|
WhipeDown*magma*Invectids under a number must be defeated several times|
BurstIn*lumens*To play the mini-game in the mountains go through the forest|
FadeToStar*igneous*You get more victory points for defeating tougher opponents|
TweenIn*hunter2*You will lose a battle if you can not draw any more cards|
WhipeToBlueStar*venus*Save your game often to keep everything you've won|
BurstIn*grasshop*Only cowards use the retreat button in combat|
FadeToBlue*shadow*Watch the Spider Riders TV series|
FadeToStar*buguese*You never know which cards your opponent will use in battle|
TweenIn*corona*The guild that helps the most during an event wins a reward|
TweenToWhite*forge*The top 5 of every guild win a prize at the end of an event|
TweenToBlue*beerain*The teacher sells very powerful cards - we must stop him|
TweenToWhite*sparkle*The top 5 of every guild win a prize at the end of an event|
WhipeUp*hunter*Each guild gives you different cards to use in battle|
WhipeDown*buguese*My cards are too powerful for you|
WhipeToBlueStar*igneous*Here's a tip: Set up deck "A" for opponents with powerful cards|
WhipeUp*aquine*You will need a well balanced deck of cards to challenge me|
TweenToBlue*venus*Play the fighting mini-game in the swamp|
TweenIn*stag*I will crush the Spider Riders!|

TweenIn*corona*Guild position after the last event: Lumen, Hunter, Igneous and Magma|
BurstIn*lumens*My Guild won the last event, I am so proud of everyone!|
WhipeUp*hunter*My guild finished second in the last event, next time we'll win!|
WhipeToBlueStar*igneous*For the last event my Guild finished third, we'll win next time|
WhipeDown*magma*I can't believe it, my guild lost the last event|

WhipeUp*hunter*Special thanks to gareiw and bamohamedalpha|
BurstIn*hunter*Thanks to kokomoha, christianhall and darkfire10x|

WhipeUp*lumens*Special thanks to venice10000000 and 97k|
BurstIn*lumens*Thanks to zatre, bluegreenmoon and legodude999|

WhipeUp*igneous*Special thanks to acetonide and ladyheat|
BurstIn*igneous*Thanks to br33zy, kingiceflame and ferrarius|

WhipeUp*magma*Special thanks to yorath and darkhan|
BurstIn*magma*Thanks to zebrahead5, pavitter and titaro2000|

WhipeDown*magma*Last Event - Top 3: gareiw, bamohamedalpha and venice10000000|
TweenToWhite*lumen*Last Event - Honorable mention: yorath and kokomoha|
FadeToStar*sparkle*The next event starts September 8th, see you there!|
FadeToStar*sparkle*The next event ends on September 15th!|
TweenToWhite*magma*My guild finished fourth in the last event|
TweenToWhite*lumens*Congratulations to my guild - we won the last event!</infopanel>

<!-- A line "|" = jump a line -->

<lockitconnect>btnReady~READY*rankName1~Trainee*rankName2~Scout*rankName3~Rider*rankName4~Warrior*rankName5~Captain*rankName6~Knight*rankName7~Commandant*rankName8~Crusader*rankName9~Champion*rankName10~Hero*gldCrdNm~ - Guild Card - *Updt~..:: ERROR ::..|WEB CONNECTION FAILED, MISSION UPGRADE WAS NOT UPDATED ON THE SERVER!|WOULD YOU LIKE TO TRY AGAIN?*errorLgnUsrnm~-INVALID USERNAME-|Do you want to register?*errorLgnPsswrd~-SORRY-|INVALID PASSWORD!*errorLgnUsrNtFnd1~-SORRY-|USERNAME NOT FOUND!*errorLgnUsrNtFnd2~-SORRY-|PLEASE REGISTER!*errorLgnAnswr~..:: ERROR ::..|SERVER DID NOT ANSWER IN TIME, PLEASE TRY AGAIN!*errorLgnSrvr~..:: SERVER SIDE ERROR ::..|type error: ? *errorSbscrbInvld1~-SORRY-|INVALID USERNAME OR PASSWORD!*errorSbscrbInvld2~PLEASE USE ONLY NUMBERS AND LETTERS WITHOUT ACCENT AND OMIT SPACES*errorSbscrbUsd~-SORRY-|THIS USERNAME IS ALREADY BEING USED!*errorSbscrbSrvr~..:: SERVER SIDE ERROR ::..|type error:*errorRfrshCnnct~..:: ERROR ::..|WEB CONNECTION FAILED, YOUR CARD DECK WAS NOT FULLY UPDATED ON THE SERVER!|WOULD YOU LIKE TO TRY AGAIN?*errorRfrshSrvr1~..:: SERVER SIDE ERROR ::..|type error:*errorRfrshSrvr2~|CARD DECK WAS NOT FULLY UPDATED ON THE SERVER!|WOULD YOU LIKE TO TRY AGAIN?*errorNwPlrCnnct~..:: ERROR ::..|WEB CONNECTION FAILED, CHARACTER AND/OR SPIDER DATA WERE NOT UPDATED ON THE SERVER!|WOULD YOU LIKE TO TRY AGAIN?*errorNwPlrSrv1~..:: SERVER SIDE ERROR ::..|type error:*errorNwPlrSrv2~|WOULD YOU LIKE TO TRY AGAIN?*infoReward~- Reward -*topFiveCard~ - Top 5 Card - *loadWorld~LOADING: WORLD OF ARACHNA*msgRankUp~RANK UPGRADE||Wonderful! You've now collected enough victory points to become a *txtEndGuild~Congratulations!|You are in this new guild.</lockitconnect>
<kitconnectmulti>nameError~..:: ERROR ::..|*nameErrLmt~..:: ERROR ::..|the user limit has been reached for this room. Spider Riders will try another one.*nameErrUsd~ is already a name used*userConnectError~..:: ERROR ::..|UNABLE TO ESTABLISH CONNECTION WITH OTHER USER!*connectError~..:: ERROR ::..|Can't establish the connection*prtnrDiscon~Your trading partner got disconnected from the game. No trade was completed.*opponentQuit~Your opponent has quit the trade module. No trade was completed.</kitconnectmulti>
<lockitcards>bugBladeCmmnt~+1 dice*arachnaNeedleCmmnt~+2 dice*lightImpalerCmmnt~+2 dice*stingslingerCmmnt~+2 dice*axialPikeCmmnt~+3 dice*swordShotCmmnt~+3 dice*theKleaverCmmnt~+4 dice*balisticMaceCmmnt~+3 dice and Remove 1 Opponent Equipment card*boomBallBowCmmnt~+3 dice and Remove 1 Opponent Boost card*spiderLanceCmmnt~+3 dice, +1 defense*oracleSpearCmmnt~+4 dice, +2 defense*heartShieldCmmnt~+1 defense*meleeShieldCmmnt~+3 defense*vanguardShieldCmmnt~+3 defense*skirmishShieldCmmnt~+2 defense*joustingShieldCmmnt~+5 defense*assaultShieldCmmnt~+6 defense*riderScaleCmmnt~+6 defense*spiderArmorCmmnt~+3 defense*elitePlateArmorCmmnt~+8 defense*redManacleCmmnt~+1 dice*blueManacleCmmnt~+4 defense*yellowManacleCmmnt~+ 5 Health Points*spyCmmnt~-1 dice to opponent*bugZapperCmmnt~+1 dice*failCmmnt~-1 dice to opponent*evasionCmmnt~-2 dice to opponent*trapCmmnt~-4 dice to opponent*falseOrderCmmnt~Counter 1 opponent battle action card*luckCmmnt~Counter 1 opponent Boost card*disarmCmmnt~Counter 1 opponent Equipment card*webTrapCmmnt~-6 dice to opponent*shadowCmmnt~-2 to defense and damage of opponent*positiveAttitudeCmmnt~Re-roll your dice*lightningBoltCmmnt~Remove all cards in game*weaponMasterCmmnt~Double damage from your dice roll*boostBlazeCmmnt~Each yellow on your dice roll count as + 2 damage*lightOfTheOracleCmmnt~Each white on your dice roll count as + 2 damage*blessingCmmnt~You may draw one card for every white and yellow you have rolled*cutiePieCmmnt~You may draw card to fill your hand*riderMasterCmmnt~All weapon Equipment card give you + 2 damage*shieldMasterCmmnt~Shield Equipment card give you + 2 defense*sparkleHelpCmmnt~Add 5 Health Points*sanctuaryCmmnt~Add 10 Health Points*giftFromOracleCmmnt~Restore all Health Points*oraclesFuryCmmnt~-6 to opponent defense*invasionCmmnt~-4 to opponent defense*bounceCmmnt~+1 dice*impactCmmnt~+1 dice*booCmmnt~+2 dice*surpriseAttackCmmnt~+2 dice*starburstCmmnt~+2 dice*deepFreezeCmmnt~+3 dice*superSizeCmmnt~+3 dice*poisonFangCmmnt~+4 dice*barbecueCmmnt~+5 dice*interventionCmmnt~+7 dice*warriorPathCmmnt~+8 dice*arachnaPowerCmmnt~+10 dice*redOracleKeyCmmnt~Merge 2 equipment weapon card*greenOracleKeyCmmnt~Merge 2 equipment defence cards*msgDelCard~Are you sure that you want to delete*msgDelCard2~Are you sure that you want to throw out*msgTradAccpt~Congratulations! Your trading partner has accepted your offer. You have traded cards with another Spider Rider!*msgTradLeav~You are leaving the trade module. No trade was completed*msgTradQuit~Quit the trade module?</lockitcards>
<lockitevents>nextEventDate~No Event in Progress*nextWednesday~Wednesday*noEvent~No Event*txt_ev3~lumens token*txt_ev6~Purple Flower*txt_ev9~Stars*txt_ev12~a Child Token*msgEventId1~Congratulations! The bridge has been rebuilt thanks to the members of your Guild. You will each receive 200 Gils.*msgEventId2~Congratulations! The prisoners were freed thanks to the members of your Guild.  You all win 3 new cards.*msgEventId3~Congratulations! Lumen has completed the challenges thanks to the members of your Guild. You each win 150 Gils.*msgEventId4~Congratulations! The Oracle celebrations can begin thanks to all the members of your Guild. You win the Positive Attitude card.*msgEventId5~Grasshop's threat was avoided thanks to all the members of your Guild. You each win 120 victory points.*msgEventId6~The epidemic caused by Beerain is over thanks to all the members of your Guild.  You have earned the Sanctuary card.*msgEventId7~The harvest crops are in the lofts thanks to the members of your Guild. As thanks, you all receive 200 Gils.*msgEventId8~Aquine's attack against the city was defeated thanks to the members of your Guild. You all earn 180 victory points.*msgEventId9~The spider race championship was won by your Guild. Each member will receive a prize of 150 Gils.*msgEventId10~Congratulations! You have won the Guilds competition thanks to the members of your Guild. The special prize is the Blessing card.*msgEventId11~The city's inhabitants were saved thanks to the members of your Guild. As a reward, you obtain the False Order and Trap cards.*msgEventId12~The school children have been saved thanks to your Guild.  You are all awarded 180 victory points.*msgEventPos1~Congratulations! Your guild has finished in first position. You are a real Spider Rider! Please accept this reward.*msgEventPos2~Hurray! Your guild has finished in second position. Thanks for your help, Spider Rider! Please accept this reward.*msgEventPos3~Good work! Your guild has finished in third position. You are on your way to become a true Spider Rider! Continue to help the Innerworld.*msgEventPos4~Nice try! Your guild has finished in fourth position. Remember that a real Spider Rider never gives up! Continue to help the Innerworld.*msgEventTop5~Congratulations, you scored in the top 5 for the last event, keep up the good work! Please accept this reward for your efforts.*msgCongrats1~Congratulations! You have earned *msgCongrats2~ for your Guild.</lockitevents>
<lockitminigames>loadingChat~LOADING: CHAT MODULE*loadingM1~LOADING: LUMEN'S RESCUE*loadingM2~LOADING: SPIDER RACES*loadingM3~LOADING: THE INVASION*loadingM4~LOADING: FOREST MONSTERS*loadingM5~LOADING: THE HUNT*loadingM6~LOADING: WRESTLING*loadingMulti~LOADING: BATTLE MULTIPLAYER</lockitminigames>
<lockitmultievents>nameArachna~Arachna Online*ev1_title~The fallen bridge*ev1_desc~The Invectids have led an attack to isolate the village and destroy the bridge*ev1_reward~200 Gils*nameEvent1~Current Event : The Fallen Bridge*nameGoal1~Bring logs to the Woodsman*ev2_title~The prisoners*ev2_desc~Mantid has ordered his troops to capture humans.*ev2_reward~Starburst, Light Impaler and Trap cards.*nameEvent2~Current Event : The Prisoners*nameGoal2~Battle Mantid Soldiers to free the prisoners*ev3_title~The Prince's holiday*ev3_desc~Help the Prince complete his training*ev3_reward~150 Gils*nameEvent3~Current Event : The Prince's Holiday*nameGoal3~Help Prince Lumen with his Training*ev4_title~Celebration of the Oracle*ev4_desc~Princess Sparkle decorates the hall for the celebration of the Oracle*ev4_reward~Positive Attitude card*nameEvent4~Current Event : Celebration of the Oracle*nameGoal4~Search for glowing rocks for the celebration of the Oracle*ev5_title~The infernal machine*ev5_desc~Stop Grasshop from building a machine designed to destroy the city*ev5_reward~120 victory points*nameEvent5~Current Event : The Infernal Machine*nameGoal5~Stop Grasshop from building his machine by defeating his soldiers*ev6_title~The epidemic*ev6_desc~Save the city from an epidemic.*ev6_reward~Sanctuary card*nameEvent6~Current Event : The Epidemic*nameGoal6~Find the purple flowers to save the city from an epidemic*ev7_title~The harvest*ev7_desc~Help the villagers store the crops from the harvest before another attack*ev7_reward~200 Gils*nameEvent7~Current Event : The Harvest*nameGoal7~Help the villagers bring in the crops before an attack from the Invectids*ev8_title~Aquine's mission*ev8_desc~Counter Aquine's attack against the city*ev8_reward~180 victory points*nameEvent8~Current Event : Aquine's mission*nameGoal8~Stop Aquine from taking over the city*ev9_title~The championship*ev9_desc~Participate in the races to determine the best driver*ev9_reward~150 Gils*nameEvent9~Current Event : The Championship*nameGoal9~Take part in the Spider Races to determine which guild has the best spider drivers*ev10_title~The Guild Competition*ev10_desc~Corona is dedicating a monument in honor of a Guild*ev10_reward~A secret prize*nameEvent10~Current Event : The Guild competition*nameGoal10~Collect as many flags as you can to help your guild*ev11_title~Grasshop's toys*ev11_desc~Grasshop has tricked the children by giving them toys that control their minds*ev11_reward~False Order and Trap cards*nameEvent11~Current Event : Grasshop's Toys*nameGoal11~Free the children from Grasshop's plan*ev12_title~Stag's Challenge*ev12_desc~Stag has captured several humans. He will return the hostages only if you prove yourself worthy in individual battle*ev12_reward~180 victory points*nameEvent12~Current Event : Stag's Challenge*nameGoal12~Defeat Stag's Soldier in challenge to rescue the prisoners*nameEvent13~Current Event : No Event Running*nameGoal13~Explore Arachna Online*nameNoEvent~There's no guild event at the moment.</lockitmultievents>
<lockitmissions>nameMis1~MISSION 1*nameMis1Goal~GOAL: TO ENTER THE TEMPLE*nameMis2~MISSION 2*nameMis2Goal~GOAL: TO DISCOVER THE ORACLE'S STATUE CHAMBER*nameMis3~MISSION 3*nameMis3Goal~GOAL: TO FIND THE MANACLE*nameMis4~MISSION 4*nameMis4Goal~GOAL: TO FIND A WAY OUT OF THE FOREST*nameMis5~MISSION 5*nameMis5Goal~GOAL: TO BOND WITH A BATTLE SPIDER AND DEFEAT THE EVIL INVECTIDS*nameMis6~MISSION 6*nameMis6Goal~GOAL: TO FREE THE PRISONERS*nameMis7~MISSION 7*nameMis7Goal~GOAL: TO SAVE THE VILLAGE*nameMis8~MISSION 8*nameMis8Goal~GOAL: TO JOIN CORONA IN THE TOWN OF ARACHNA*nameMis9~MISSION 9*nameMis9Goal~GOAL: COMPLETE SPIDER RIDER TRAINING*nameMis10~MISSION 10*nameMis10Goal~GOAL: FIND THE SPY INSIDE THE FORTRESS*nameMis11~MISSION 11*nameMis11Goal~GOAL: WIN A DUEL*nameMis12~MISSION 12*nameMis12Goal~GOAL: TO PROTECT THE TURANDOT PEOPLE OF ARACHNA*nameMis13~MISSION 13*nameMis13Goal~GOAL: DEFEAT GRASSHOP AND HIS MONSTER*nameMis14~MISSION 14*nameMis14Goal~GOAL: FIND CORONA*nameMis15~MISSION 15*nameMis15Goal~GOAL: FIND THE CARDS!*nameMisEnd~CONGRATULATIONS ON COMPLETING THE MISSIONS!*txtM1Z1_p1~You can move by clicking on the square that you want to move to.*txtM1Z2_p1~To pick something up, you must go to the square where the object is.*txtM1Z3_p1~You have completed the first mission.You are on your way to becoming a great Spider Rider!*txtM1Z4_p1~Click on an object in your backpack, then place it where you would like to use it.*txtM1Z4_p2~Ropes are great for climbing up walls!*txtM1Z4_p3~Click on the rope in your backpack and place it on the wall.*txtM2Z1_p1~You've just found a Boost card! It will help you during battles by increasing the strength of your attacks.*txtM2Z2_p1~Careful! You must defeat a creature that can attack you by rolling the dice.*txtM2Z2_p2~Each opponent plays in turn.*txtM2Z2_p3~The game will now determine who starts.*txtM2Z3_p1~You have completed the second mission. You make a great Spider Rider!*txtM3Z1_p1~I... talk to you... Have to... You are... too far... bring... Manacle...*txtM3Z2_p1~You have completed the third mission.*txtM3Z4_p1~Congratulations! You've found the Manacle!*txtM3Z3_p1~Thank you for finding the Manacle. It will allow me to make a connection with you.*txtM3Z3_p2~I've been waiting for you for a long time. But I can't talk to you for very long.*txtM3Z3_p3~Trust me. Come and join us. Our world needs your help.*txtM3Z3_p4~Please, go through the portal.*txtM4Z1_p1~I found this key in the forest while picking flowers. I think it belongs to the lumberjack.*txtM4Z1_p2~He must have hidden in the village during the attack.*txtM4Z1_p3~Thank you for saving me. I was in the forest when the Invectids attacked. I didn't hear the warning.*txtM4Z1_p4~The doors to the village are now closed. I must hide. See you later, Stranger.*txtM4Z1_p5~See you later, Stranger. I hope our paths will cross once again.*txtM4Z2_p1~There was an axe inside the lumberjack's house!*txtM4Z3_p1~You should not have come into this forest, Stranger!*txtM4Z4_p1~You've just found an Equipment card.*txtM4Z4_p2~You can play this card during battles when you get a green die.*txtM4Z5_p1~Enemy alert!*txtM4Z6_p1~You have completed the fourth mission.*txtM5Z1_p1~I see you're wearing a Manacle?  Thanks to Manacles such as these Spider Riders have been able to bond with their battle spiders.*txtM5Z1_p2~Are you a Spider Rider too? Where's your spider?*txtM5Z1_p3~Thank you for finding this medicinal plant.*txtM5Z1_p4~Thanks to you, I can make my medicinal balm that will save the young warrior.*txtM5Z1_p5~Thank you for finding this medicinal plant.*txtM5Z1_p6~Unfortunately, I lost my tool bag and I'm afraid of going back inside the forest to find it.*txtM5Z1_p7~You managed to find my bag.*txtM5Z1_p8~Thanks to you, I can make my medicinal balm that will save the young warrior.*txtM5Z1_p9~You managed to find my bag.*txtM5Z1_p10~Now I need a purple flower. They say they grow in dark caves.*txtM5Z2_p1~There is a wounded warrior in the forest.*txtM5Z2_p2~I must help him, but I need a purple flower to make medicine.*txtM5Z2_p3~I also lost my bag with all of my tools.*txtM5Z2_p4~When you have found your spider, use your Manacle to talk to it.*txtM5Z3_p1~This manacle does not allow you to open these doors.*txtM5Z4_p1~The Invectids have launched another attack. The doors must remain closed to ensure that Arachna is safe.*txtM5Z4_p2~The doors will remain closed as long as the Invectid commander and his monster are in the forest.*txtM5Z5_p1~Move along. I don't want to talk to you.*txtM5Z6_p1~What's happening? I hear the Oracle's voice. She says you are on your way to becoming a Spider Rider. I will join you in this adventure to the very end.*txtM5Z7_p1~Poor fool! Go tell your people this forest now belongs to us.*txtM5Z8_p1~They're invincible... Retreat!*txtM5Z8_p2~Hummm... You don't look like the Turandots, do you? Our master was right: there's an intruder in the forest.*txtM5Z8_p3~I'd get a reward for catching you. Charge!*txtM5Z9_p1~I owe you my life, Stranger. I will never forget it.*txtM5Z9_p2~Here's a key I found in the forest.  This may be useful for you.*txtM5Z10_p1~The Invectids... They attacked me... I'm... wounded...*txtM5Z10_p2~The Invectid commander uses his Monster to help him control the forest. We're caught in a trap. Only a Spider Rider could defeat him.*txtM5Z11_p1~My key! At last! But I can't go back home. The forest is crawling with Invectids.*txtM5Z11_p2~But YOU have to return. I can lend you my axe to defend yourself.*txtM5Z11_p3~Please, noble warrior, protect us from the Invectids.*txtM5Z12_p1~I lost the key to my house and I don't think the forest is safe. Luckily, I found my axe.*txtM5Z12_p2~This rope looks like the ones we use to climb the face of the mountain.*txtM6Z1_p1~Who are you?*txtM6Z1_p2~Some villagers told me that an unknown Spider Rider won the latest Invectid attack. If that's the case, you truly deserve to be a part of our team.*txtM6Z1_p3~I don't have time to go with you to the Fortress and introduce you to the Prince. I must complete my mission first.*txtM6Z1_p4~You've managed to tame a spider. This will help you during battle. Your spider can also help you go to many places.*txtM6Z1_p5~With the spider's web, you can climb walls and jump over holes in the ground.*txtM6Z2_p1~Have you seen any people around here?*txtM6Z2_p2~Since the Invectids attacked, some of the villagers have been missing. I fear something terrible may have happened to them.*txtM6Z2_p3~We must find them quickly.*txtM6Z3_p1~I saw another warrior go through the forest. Maybe he was looking for you.*txtM6Z4_p1~I can help you even outside battles. My web is very strong, you'll see.*txtM6Z5_p1~The doors to the village will stay closed until we find our missing family and friends.*txtM6Z5_p2~They had gone to go pick medicine plants to heal our wounded.*txtM6Z5_p3~But they never came back from that trip.*txtM6Z6_p1~Alert! A Spider Rider!*txtM6Z7_p1~My friends have been taken prisoner in the cave by those monsters.*txtM6Z7_p2~Please save them!*txtM6Z8_p1~We've been saved!*txtM7Z1_p1~You're a warrior too.*txtM7Z1_p2~Your spider is wonderful. You should go see my brother. He could train you to become a true Spider Rider warrior.*txtM7Z2_p1~I've never seen you before.*txtM7Z3_p1~Fortunately, the prisoners are safe and sound!*txtM7Z3_p2~We must get some tools from the shopkeeper to stop the Invectids.*txtM7Z3_p3~But I don't know how to battle.*txtM7Z4_p1~I can't face the Invectids without my spider that they've captured.*txtM7Z4_p2~You're our only hope of stopping them.*txtM7Z4_p3~But you must find better equipment. The shopkeeper can sell you this equipment.*txtM7Z4_p4~... but, you have to buy it!*txtM7Z4_p5~I tried to stop the Invectids from entering the village...*txtM7Z4_p6~But the Invectid beat me and took my spider. I'm no match for him alone.*txtM7Z4_p7~The Invectids are too powerful. You don't have enough equipment to put up a good fight.*txtM7Z5_p1~Now we must drive out the Invectids!*txtM7Z5_p2~We're doomed.*txtM7Z6_p1~Our fate will now be decided in the village.*txtM7Z6_p2~Do you have everything you need to free the villagers?*txtM7Z6_p3~With your help, I was able to start working again. I make wood boards to repair the houses in the village.*txtM7Z7_p1~I wanted to see if the villagers were trapped inside the cave, but the Invectids attacked the village...*txtM7Z7_p2~I wanted to protect my house. I can give you my Pick if you want.*txtM7Z8_p1~I have bad news.*txtM7Z8_p2~The Invectids have launched a surprise attack against the village. They ran in with their monster when we opened the doors.*txtM7Z8_p3~A warrior tried to drive them back, but he didn't succeed.*txtM7Z8_p4~They need your help.*txtM7Z9_p1~The prisoners will soon be free.*txtM7Z9_p2~Only fire can break this Invectid's web.*txtM7Z9_p3~The bridge seems sturdy enough to let the prisoners across, but we must destroy this web.*txtM7Z9_p4~Without fire, it's impossible.*txtM7Z9_p5~Your spider's web is not strong enough to let through the people trapped in the cave.*txtM7Z9_p6~We have to build a bridge with a wood board to help them across...*txtM7Z9_p7~... and clear the path that was blocked by the web and the rocks.*txtM7Z9_p8~Only fire can break this Invectid's web.*txtM7Z10_p1~The prisoners are on their way back. You've managed to protect us once again.*txtM7Z10_p2~You've already cleared part of the path. I see a prisoner. Have you found everything you need to help them out?*txtM7Z11_p1~Let's get out of here*txtM7Z12_p1~Here, Stranger. Take this ring. Give it to my husband to show him that I'm still alive.*txtM7Z13_p1~I want to go back home.*txtM7Z13_p2~I will see my father again. I'm sure he will reward you.*txtM7Z14_p1~I'm afraid that I'll never see my dad again.*txtM7Z14_p2~We are going back to the village.*txtM7Z15_p1~We can't break out of this cave.*txtM7Z15_p2~The hole in the ground is blocking our way... We could cross with a wood board.*txtM7Z15_p3~But we also must clear the path.*txtM7Z15_p4~We're trapped.*txtM7Z15_p5~You did it!*txtM7Z16_p1~We have been ordered not to let any strangers through.*txtM7Z17_p1~We are waiting for Princess Sparkle to return.*txtM7Z18_p1~I hear shouts of joy in the village. Perhaps the Spider Riders have managed to chase our enemies away!*txtM7Z18_p2~The shopkeeper has entered his shop. Is he the bearer of good news?*txtM7Z18_p3~The Invectids have finally managed to invade the village. They will destroy our land once again.*txtM7Z19_p1~This ring belongs to my wife! Is she OK? If you need anything, come see me.*txtM7Z20_p1~I can't open my shop. My wife is missing in the mountains. I must go look for her.*txtM7Z21_p1~The prisoners are free!*txtM7Z21_p2~Are you going to face the Invectid Champion*txtM7Z21_p3~The Invectids have invaded the village and the Spider Riders aren't doing anything!*txtM7Z22_p1~Look at the Champion they sent us.*txtM7Z22_p2~He looks like a baby.*txtM7Z22_p3~Our warrior will defeat him no problem!*txtM7Z22_p4~Get out of here, you rat! Don't even think of tackling our Champion. He'll break you in half!*txtM7Z22_p5~Our warrior will defeat him no problem!*txtM7Z23_p1~You've completed mission #7. Congratulations!*txtM7Z23_p2~I see you're all set for battle.*txtM7Z23_p3~Be careful, this is a fearsome enemy.*txtM7Z23_p4~Stay close to your spider. And good luck.*txtM7Z24_p1~This is a sad day.*txtM7Z25_p1~A warrior must defeat the Invectids.*txtM7Z26_p1~Here is what you'll need.*txtM8Z1_p1~It will be dark soon and the forest is not a safe place. I ordered the doors be closed.*txtM8Z1_p2~I think you need a place to sleep for the night.*txtM8Z1_p3~Come with me to the Fortress. We should be able to find you a room.*txtM8Z1_p4~Before we go, I'd like to give this flower to the Healer.*txtM8Z1_p5~Can you help me?*txtM8Z2_p1~I closed the gate to make sure the village is safe during the night.*txtM8Z3_p1~We've been ordered to let no one through.*txtM8Z3_p2~Our guard duty is over.*txtM8Z4_p1~We are waiting for Princess Sparkle. It will be dark soon and the forest is not a safe place. I ordered the doors be closed.*txtM8Z4_p2~It's time to go home now.*txtM8Z5_p1~Come meet me inside the fortress.*txtM8Z6_p1~Everybody go home.*txtM8Z7_p1~I'm happy that one of my kind has chosen to honor the people of Arachna, the Turandots.*txtM8Z7_p2~Watch your Spider very carefully.*txtM8Z7_p3~You are now bound together for life.*txtM8Z8_p1~The night is coming and it has been a hard day. We need to rest.*txtM8Z9_p1~It will be dark soon. Do you have a place to sleep?*txtM8Z9_p2~I invite you inside the Fortress with the other Spider Riders.*txtM8Z9_p3~Meet me in front of the doors to the town of Arachna.*txtM8Z10_p1~Mom, did you see the spiders fight? They're unbelievable!*txtM8Z11_p1~Thanks for giving me this flower. I can use it to heal my people.*txtM8Z11_p2~You've done a lot for us since you come here. It must mean great things for you.*txtM8Z11_p3~I believe the Oracle is guiding you along.*txtM8Z11_p4~We are in a safe place, but it has been ruined by Buguese, leader of the Invectids.*txtM8Z11_p5~He broke the statue containing the Oracle's spirit and scattered the pieces all over...*txtM8Z11_p6~But they won't succeed!*txtM8Z11_p7~The legend tells of a stranger coming here to save our people and defeat the forces of Mantid, the Invectid Leader.*txtM8Z11_p8~I believe that day will soon come.*txtM8Z12_p1~I have come to thank the Oracle for protecting us today.*txtM8Z12_p2~I'm going home now to prepare a potion with this flower.*txtM8Z13_p1~Welcome to the town of Arachna!*txtM9Z1_p1~Here we are in the town of Arachna, ruled by Prince Lumen.*txtM9Z1_p2~This town is in the heart of Turandot country. It is protected by a small group of fighters called the Spider Riders.*txtM9Z1_p3~We're part of a group of warriors, but we need more Spider Riders!*txtM9Z1_p4~I want you to meet the Prince. I must be sure of one thing before I take you to him: do you have what it takes to become a true Spider Rider?*txtM9Z1_p5~The only way to find out is to challenge you to a battle. How about a friendly duel inside the Coliseum? But it's getting late and the doors must be closed.*txtM9Z1_p6~We need to ask the guard to open the Coliseum doors for our battle.*txtM9Z2_p1~It's too late now to leave town.*txtM9Z3_p1~I am guarding the entrance to the town. If you are looking for the Coliseum doors, just go to the end of this street.*txtM9Z3_p2~It's too late now to leave town.*txtM9Z4_p1~Here we are in the town of Arachna, ruled by Prince Lumen.*txtM9Z4_p2~This town is in the heart of Turandot country. It is protected by a small group of fighters called the Spider Riders.*txtM9Z4_p3~We're part of a group of warriors, but we need more Spider Riders!*txtM9Z4_p4~I want you to meet the Prince. I must be sure of one thing before I take you to him: do you have what it takes to become a true Spider Rider?*txtM9Z4_p5~The only way to find out is to challenge you to a battle. How about a friendly duel inside the Coliseum? But it's getting late and the doors must be closed.*txtM9Z4_p6~We need to ask the guard to open the Coliseum doors for our battle.*txtM9Z5_p1~I'm glad to be in this safe place.*txtM9Z6_p1~I know everyone in this town. You're not from around here, are you?*txtM9Z7_p1~I'm closing my shop, but you can come back tomorrow if you need anything.*txtM9Z8_p1~Time to go home.*txtM9Z8_p2~Now there's a true warrior!*txtM9Z8_p3~I bet you're looking for the keys to the Coliseum doors.*txtM9Z8_p4~Here they are. Have a great battle.*txtM9Z9_p1~I shut down my store and I'm going home.*txtM9Z10_p1~My parents tell me never to talk to strangers.*txtM9Z11_p1~I like watching the water flow from the fountain.*txtM9Z12_p1~The audience is over.*txtM9Z13_p1~Prince Lumen sees no one at this hour.*txtM9Z14_p1~I must go back to my family.*txtM9Z15_p1~Careful! You're facing a true Spider Rider.*txtM9Z15_p2~Corona is an excellent fighter who has cards she can play in battle.*txtM9Z15_p3~Good luck!*txtM9Z15_p4~You found the keys!*txtM9Z15_p5~We can go in and have a battle.*txtM9Z15_p6~Beware, I won't go easy on you.*txtM9Z16_p1~We are in front of the Coliseum but the doors are closed. If I had the keys, I could enter and challenge you in a friendly duel.*txtM9Z17_p1~Can I help you? I make all kinds of objects.*txtM10Z1_p1~No use going any further.*txtM10Z2_p1~All is quiet in the town tonight.*txtM10Z3_p1~You are one of Prince Lumen's guests. You can go ahead.*txtM10Z4_p1~You can't come in*txtM10Z4_p2~The guards have not seen anything in the town*txtM10Z5_p1~Strangers are not allowed inside the fortress.*txtM10Z5_p2~The guards have not seen anything in the town*txtM10Z6_p1~I don't understand why you need the keys to the Fortress.*txtM10Z6_p2~But since Corona herself has asked...*txtM10Z7_p1~You did very well. I'm sure the other Spider Riders will like you.*txtM10Z7_p2~Let's meet inside the Fortress. I will find you a room so you can sleep.*txtM10Z7_p3~Take this seal. You can give it to the guards posted in front of the Fortress.*txtM10Z8_p1~You make a good team, but next time we'll win.*txtM10Z9_p1~I must do some work in my shop. Come see me tomorrow.*txtM10Z10_p1~The doors to the Hall have been closed for a long time.*txtM10Z10_p2~Prince Lumen is out riding his spider for a bit of exercise.*txtM10Z11_p1~I'm glad you've come all the way here. This is Hortala, my spider.*txtM10Z11_p2~I hope you will stay with us for a long time. You'll see, we're going to have lots of fun.*txtM10Z12_p1~Grriw... Griw...*txtM10Z13_p1~I searched the other rooms and there's no trace of the spy. This is the only room left.*txtM10Z13_p2~Sadly, I don't have the key to the Princess' room.*txtM10Z14_p1~Door unlocked.*txtM10Z15_p1~Miss Corona has asked that a room be prepared for you.*txtM10Z16_p1~You've just found your very first Battle Action card.*txtM10Z16_p2~With these cards, you can do special things during battles.*txtM10Z17_p1~I think I heard somebody moving around on the balcony.*txtM10Z18_p1~There you are!*txtM10Z18_p2~I've asked that a guest room be set up for you.*txtM10Z18_p3~Here's the key.*txtM10Z19_p1~I came right away when I heard sounds of people fighting.*txtM10Z19_p2~You were dealing with a spy under the Invectids' control.*txtM10Z19_p3~He must still be inside the Fortress. Hurry, we must find him!*txtM10Z20_p1~My master wants you to follow me to the hive.*txtM10Z20_p2~Never!*txtM10Z20_p3~Don't try to fight me.. No one can save you.*txtM10Z21_p1~You've completed Mission #10. Congratulations!*txtM11Z1_p1~It's been a quiet night. My watch duty is over. I can go to bed.*txtM11Z2_p1~What a great day!*txtM11Z3_p1~I made this armor to protect the Spider Riders' spiders. It's for sale, if you want it.*txtM11Z4_p1~I love to start work bright and early in the morning.*txtM11Z5_p1~I made this armor to protect the Spider Riders' spiders. It's for sale, if you want it.*txtM11Z6_p1~Igneous has left the Fortress and is on his way to the Coliseum.*txtM11Z7_p1~This morning, Prince Lumen has guests in the Hall.*txtM11Z8_p1~Be wary of Igneous. He's an excellent fighter, but he's very sure of himself. If you face him in battle, you'd be wise to be better equipped.*txtM11Z8_p2~You've completed Mission #11. Congratulations!*txtM11Z8_p3~Igneous is waiting for you in the Coliseum.*txtM11Z8_p4~He is strong and brave but he doesn't do any favors.*txtM11Z8_p5~Good luck!*txtM11Z9_p1~Corona seems to be worried for you.*txtM11Z10_p1~If you want this Manacle, it's yours!*txtM11Z11_p1~Hello stranger. You've come to see what I have to sell?*txtM11Z12_p1~This Manacle has great powers.*txtM11Z13_p1~Prince Lumen would like to thank you for protecting his sister.*txtM11Z14_p1~Whatever next! The Prince wants you to join our team! You need a lesson in defeat. I challenge you on the sands of the Coliseum to see if you have real Spider Rider skills.*txtM11Z15_p1~I'd love for you to join our group. We need more brave warriors to protect our country.*txtM11Z15_p2~So there you are.*txtM11Z15_p3~My sister Sparkle told me how you got her out of trouble last night.*txtM11Z15_p4~You showed great courage. As a gesture of thanks, I'd like to offer you a reward.*txtM11Z15_p5~Corona claims you can fight like a true Spider Rider.*txtM11Z15_p6~My team is in need of more warriors. Would you like to join us?*txtM11Z15_p7~We could help you complete your training.*txtM11Z16_p1~We thank you in the name of the royal family.*txtM11Z17_p1~Hmm... Another pair.*txtM11Z18_p1~Hello, Stranger.*txtM11Z18_p2~We are waiting for you in the Hall.*txtM11Z18_p3~The Prince would like to reward you for your great deeds.*txtM11Z18_p4~But don't forget: it's not just anybody who can be a Spider Rider.*txtM11Z19_p1~Rise and shine! I hope you slept well.*txtM11Z19_p2~Now hurry up. The Prince is waiting for you in the Hall.*txtM11Z19_p3~He wants to reward you for your deeds yesterday.*txtM11Z20_p1~I slept pretty well in spite of the scare that horrible grasshopper gave me.*txtM11Z20_p2~Thank you for saving my life.*txtM11Z21_p1~Welcome to my shop.*txtM11Z22_p1~This weapon suits you perfectly, if you want to buy it.*txtM11Z23_p1~This weapon suits you perfectly, if you want to buy it.*txtM12Z1_p1~I'll stay on my guard. The Invectids will no longer come through the town doors!*txtM12Z1_p2~Here's another one!*txtM12Z1_p3~They took me by surprise! I can't stop them!*txtM12Z1_p4~Here's an another one!*txtM12Z2_p1~I wonder why the rules force us to control access to the town.*txtM12Z2_p2~It's very boring.*txtM12Z2_p3~I think I heard something move in the bushes.*txtM12Z2_p4~It's probably just the wind.*txtM12Z3_p1~Today, I'm going to the village to visit my brother.*txtM12Z3_p2~I heard they got a very close look at the Invectids.*txtM12Z3_p3~I hear strange noises. I think we should alert the Spider Riders.*txtM12Z4_p1~Help!*txtM12Z5_p1~The door is unlocked.*txtM12Z6_p1~I'm working on a new armor. Come see me later if you'd like to buy it.*txtM12Z7_p1~Watch out!*txtM12Z7_p2~I'm surrounded!*txtM12Z7_p3~Here's comes the last one!*txtM12Z8_p1~Here's another one!*txtM12Z8_p2~I'm surrounded!*txtM12Z8_p3~Here's another one!*txtM12Z9_p1~There's a lot of work to do in the gardens. I'll tell the Fortress people.*txtM12Z10_p1~Some of the Turandots are still missing.*txtM12Z10_p2~You've completed Mission #12. Congratulations!*txtM12Z10_p3~All the Turandots are inside the Fortress.*txtM12Z10_p4~We can close the doors to protect the Turandots.*txtM12Z11_p1~We need to relieve the guard at the town entrance. That old fool is sleeping on his spear.*txtM12Z11_p2~Something's brewing. We need to warn Master Igneous.*txtM12Z11_p3~Most of the townspeople are inside, but some of the Turandots are still in the streets!*txtM12Z12_p1~What a great battle!*txtM12Z12_p2~That signal! The Invectids must surely be attacking!*txtM12Z12_p3~Venus and I will go patrol the town.*txtM12Z13_p1~You fought a clean fight. I must admit the others were right.*txtM12Z13_p2~You may be worthy of the title of Spider Rider.*txtM12Z13_p3~I would be proud to accept you to our team.*txtM12Z13_p4~Can you hear that noise? The town is under attack!*txtM12Z13_p5~Hurry, the townspeople must head for cover inside the Fortress.*txtM12Z14_p1~Find that woman, please!*txtM12Z14_p2~A friend of mine is still inside her house. Take this key and go see if she was captured by those monsters.*txtM12Z14_p3~Here's another one!*txtM12Z14_p4~Save me!*txtM12Z15_p1~I hope the Manacle you bought was useful.*txtM12Z15_p2~Where does that noise come from?*txtM13Z1_p1~I can handle their troops, but I'm a little busy.*txtM13Z1_p2~And we have another major problem on our hands. Can you handle it?*txtM13Z2_p1~A monster is destroying our town!*txtM13Z3_p1~We have to strike back at the Invectids as soon as possible!*txtM13Z4_p1~That wasn't enough, was it? Alright. Fire!*txtM13Z4_p2~Stupid Spider Rider! Maybe you managed to beat my monster, but you don't stand a chance against my arsenal.*txtM13Z5_p1~You've completed Mission #13. Congratulations!*txtM13Z5_p2~You won this battle, Spider Rider. But we'll be back to drive the Turandots out of the world of Arachna!*txtM13Z5_p3~Step back, dumb human... I order you to move back...*txtM13Z6_p1~I think Igneous has the situation under control.*txtM13Z7_p1~The Invectid's attack is threatening the town.*txtM13Z8_p1~The Invectids are destroying the town.*txtM13Z9_p1~The townspeople are safe and sound inside the fortress.*txtM13Z10_p1~Our houses will be destroyed.*txtM13Z11_p1~The Spider Riders will drive out our enemies.*txtM14Z1_p1~I'm going fishing while my mother works in the garden.*txtM14Z1_p2~You saw my mother go inside to prepare a healing potion.*txtM14Z1_p3~Hurry, I must tend to the fire or else she will scold me.*txtM14Z1_p4~We'll go fishing another time.*txtM14Z2_p1~A warrior came to the village, but she didn't stay very long.*txtM14Z2_p2~She went into the forest.*txtM14Z3_p1~The Spider Riders were successful in driving back the Invectids for good.*txtM14Z4_p1~I think the healer went to see her plants this morning.*txtM14Z4_p2~I just saw the healer as she was going home.*txtM14Z5_p1~I would like to become a Spider Rider like you one day.*txtM14Z6_p1~Thanks to you, I was able to prepare a supply of medicine. One bottle of this medicine belongs to you.*txtM14Z7_p1~Of course, I can sell you this tool.*txtM14Z8_p1~Hello.*txtM14Z9_p1~Thanks for the flower. It will help me to make medicine. But I still need three flowers to make it.*txtM14Z9_p2~I still need two flowers to make this medicine.*txtM14Z9_p3~I only need one flower to make this medicine.*txtM14Z9_p4~I can now go home to make the medicine.*txtM14Z9_p5~I hope my son kept the fire burning. I need lots of heat to prepare this potion.*txtM14Z10_p1~Hello, Stranger. What a great day for gardening.*txtM14Z11_p1~I hope you find Corona.*txtM14Z12_p1~Prince Lumen asked to speak to you.*txtM14Z13_p1~The town seems safe now. The Turandots can leave the Fortress.*txtM14Z14_p1~We made it through once again.*txtM14Z15_p1~Mother, come see outside!*txtM14Z16_p1~Are we out of danger?*txtM14Z17_p1~Come quickly! Prince Lumen would like to speak to you.*txtM14Z18_p1~Our warriors drove back the Invectids once again.*txtM14Z19_p1~My necklace! Thank you, stranger. Here, take these Gils as a token of my gratitude.*txtM14Z20_p1~I hope the craftsman will be able to deliver the necklace I ordered. I am looking forward to receiving it.*txtM14Z21_p1~What a fight!*txtM14Z21_p2~What has gotten into our enemies?*txtM14Z22_p1~You and your Spider Rider defended yourselves well.*txtM14Z23_p1~Those monsters turned my shop upside down.*txtM14Z23_p2~Luckily, they didn't damage my work.*txtM14Z23_p3~We should bring this necklace to the woman who ordered it.*txtM14Z24_p1~Do you know where Corona is?*txtM14Z25_p1~I have a bad feeling.*txtM14Z26_p1~I saw a warrior go through the forest. I think she was chasing an enemy.*txtM14Z27_p1~There you are!*txtM14Z27_p2~I think we have another problem on our hands.*txtM14Z27_p3~Corona is nowhere to be found since the Invectids attacked.*txtM14Z27_p4~We must check the plains to see if she needs help.*txtM14Z28_p1~You were very brave. But I fear our problems are not over yet.*txtM14Z29_p1~Fortunately, you found us. We followed a warrior woman all the way to this marsh.*txtM14Z29_p2~But one of Mantid's monsters took us by surprise. Corona has been hurt.*txtM14Z29_p3~We must go get medicine for her.*txtM14Z30_p1~It's a trap!*txtM14Z31_p1~Thank you... This potion works really well, but I'm still too weak.*txtM14Z31_p2~The Invectids have ordered a monster to guard the marsh.*txtM14Z31_p3~You must not stay here.*txtM14Z31_p4~Go get some help.*txtM14Z31_p5~What's that noise?*txtM14Z31_p6~The monster is coming back!*txtM14Z31_p7~Run away quickly or else it will be too late.*txtM14Z32_p1~Stop the fight!*txtM14Z32_p2~You fought well, Spider Rider, but you're still no match for me.*txtM14Z32_p3~My master heard you were coming to this world.*txtM14Z32_p4~He knows the legend that tells of a human from the outside world coming to save the Turandots from destruction.*txtM14Z32_p5~You ruin our plans, so listen to me: do not stand in my way or you will have to deal with me.*txtM14Z32_p6~Return to your town! Go tell your Prince that the Invectids are going to win this war.*txtM14Z32_p7~The world of Arachna will soon belong to my Mantid.*txtM14Z32_p8~Too late, Spider Rider. You will pay the price for not minding your own business. Prepare to die!*txtM14Z32_p9~Stop! You can't fight her alone.*txtM14Z32_p10~I am Aquine. I was raised by Mantid to destroy the Spider Riders. She is mine.*txtM14Z33_p1~Leave this area... My patience is running out!*txtM14Z34_p1~Next time, I will crush you.*txtM14Z35_p1~I'm hurt. I can't move. Go... It's too dangerous...*txtM14Z35_p2~It's too late. Run away!*txtM14Z35_p3~We must go find Prince Lumen.*txtM14Z36_p1~She needs to regain her strength.*txtM14Z36_p2~Go get some help while I watch over Corona.*txtM14Z36_p3~Let's get out of this marsh quickly.*txtM14Z37_p1~You've completed Mission #14. Congratulations!*txtM14Z37_p2~There you are!*txtM14Z37_p3~I have had to clear the rocks that were blocking the path to join you.*txtM14Z37_p4~Come, the path is clear!*txtM15Z0_p1~Bonus level : To finish the game, find the cards scattered all over the town of Arachna.*txtM15Z0_p2~We are gathered here to welcome a new recruit to our company.*txtM15Z0_p3~You have shown your worth once again.*txtM15Z0_p4~I am happy to welcome you among us.*txtM15Z0_p5~Our enemies' words seem to say that the war is far from over.*txtM15Z0_p6~We will need you and anyone else who has the courage to join us.*txtM15Z0_p7~All for one and one for all, calling all Spider Riders!*txtM15Z1_p1~Glory and honor to the heroes of Arachna!*txtM15Z2_p1~Thanks to you, we are safe and sound.*txtM15Z3_p1~You have completed the solo missions.*txtM15Z3_p2~Come join us in the world of Arachna to continue the adventure.*txtM15Z3_p3~See you soon, Spider Rider!*txtM15Z4_p1~The armor isn't ready yet.*txtM15Z4_p2~In the meantime, I finished this armor. It's yours in exchange for this loose change.*txtM15Z5_p1~Thank you for doing what you do.*txtM15Z6_p1~May the Oracle watch over you.*txtM15Z7_p1~Everything is back to normal in the town.*txtM15Z8_p1~The craftsman finished making my ring. How nice.*txtM15Z8_p2~Oh, come to think of it... I also have a gift for you.*txtM15Z8_p3~It's not much, but please take these.*txtM15Z9_p1~Thank you for all that you've done for me.*txtM15Z10_p1~Hello, noble Spider Rider. Thank you for protecting our houses.*txtM15Z11_p1~Of course, I have something that may interest you.*txtM15Z11_p2~I also know a woman who would like to express her thanks.*txtM15Z11_p3~Since I need to bring her this ring, maybe you can take it to her yourself.*txtM15Z12_p1~Thank you for protecting our houses.*txtM15Z13_p1~Now that it's all over, I can go rest.*txtM15Z14_p1~Congratulations!*txtM15Z15_p1~You're one of us now.*txtM15Z16_p1~It's wonderful.*txtM15Z17_p1~The door is locked.*txt_cp1_bkg12_1_1~This new barrier will make it more difficult for the Invectids to invade us*txt_cp1_bkg12_2_1~Snif I fell while playing snif... My foot hurts real bad*txt_cp1_bkg12_2_2~Snif The healer will help me  Snif But I think it will hurt*txt_cp1_bkg13_1_1~A bottle, thank you very much young Spider Rider.*txt_cp1_bkg13_1_2~But I must help a child that is injured.*txt_cp1_bkg13_1_3~Can you bring this potion to the man that lives in the forest?*txt_cp1_bkg13_2_1~I have to go help the man who lives in the forest*txt_cp1_bkg13_2_2~But I hear a child crying in the village*txt_cp1_bkg13_2_3~I will need a bottle to bring a potion to the man that lives in the forest.*txt_cp1_bkg13_2_4~Thanks for bringing me the bottle.*txt_cp1_bkg13_3_1~You will not succeed in saving your friend.*txt_cp1_bkg14_1_1~We have come for the traitor.*txt_cp1_bkg14_1_2~She will suffer the wrath of our master.*txt_cp1_bkg14_1_3~Get out of our way or you will suffer the same consequences.*txt_cp1_bkg14_2_1~Thank you.*txt_cp1_bkg14_2_2~The soldier had come to arrest me, but I'm sure others will follow.*txt_cp1_bkg14_2_3~I have to see a friend in the village, but I am afraid.*txt_cp1_bkg14_2_4~Will you accompany me to the village?*txt_cp1_bkg16_1_1~Your friends will not stop me from bringing you to my master, you traitor.*txt_cp1_bkg16_1_2~Monster, attack!*txt_cp1_bkg16_1_3~I beg you, do not put yourself in danger for me. *txt_cp1_bkg16_2_1~Great battle Spider Rider.*txt_cp1_bkg16_3_1~You have saved me once again.*txt_cp1_bkg16_3_2~Thanks to you I can continue my fight to bring our people together.*txt_cp1_bkg16_4_1~Mission Complete. Congratulations!*txt_cp1_bkg18_1_1~I told the healer that the woodsman was very sick*txt_cp1_bkg18_1_2~I hope the woodsman is doing well.*txt_cp1_bkg18_1_3~The healer wants to know if the woodsman is feeling better. *txt_cp1_bkg22_1_1~Thanks for making me feel better!*txt_cp1_bkg22_2_1~Thanks for giving the woodsman the potion.*txt_cp1_bkg22_2_2~You can relax and have some fun now. *txt_cp1_bkg22_2_3~Someone is waiting for you at the Inn.*txt_cp1_bkg22_3_1~I hope to get some news for Brutus regarding his sister Portia. *txt_cp1_bkg22_3_2~I am going to speak to the villagers*txt_cp1_bkg22_3_3~I will meet you at the Inn, there is someone I want to introduce to you.*txt_cp1_bkg22_3_4~In the meantime here is some gil in case you need to get something from a shopkeeper. *txt_cp1_bkg22_4_1~Hurry the Invectids have taken Cathy.*txt_cp1_bkg23_1_1~Here is what you can buy with that amount of gil.*txt_cp1_bkg23_2_1~I have to organize my shop.*txt_cp1_bkg23_2_2~What is that noise coming from outside? It sounds like a child is crying.*txt_cp1_bkg23_2_3~What would you like to buy?*txt_cp1_bkg23_2_4~Are you looking for something?*txt_cp1_bkg46_1_1~Come on in and have a seat.*txt_cp1_bkg46_1_2~We are not opened yet, please come back later.*txt_cp1_bkg46_2_1~But my dear, I have the right to have some fun.*txt_cp1_bkg46_2_2~What are you still doing here ? There is still a lot of work to do in the fields*txt_cp1_bkg46_3_1~Oh no, not again!*txt_cp1_bkg46_3_2~Do you hear that noise?*txt_cp1_bkg46_3_3~My people are blinded by Mantid.*txt_cp1_bkg46_3_4~They do not understand that we could live in peace with humans*txt_cp1_bkg46_3_5~This war has gone on long enough.*txt_cp1_bkg46_3_6~Did the soldiers attack you ?*txt_cp1_bkg46_3_7~We already know each other. It's with the help of this Spider Rider that I was able to escape the Invectids.*txt_cp1_bkg46_3_8~Let me introduce you to Cathy.*txt_cp1_bkg60_1_1~AhhhChoo*txt_cp1_bkg60_1_2~I feel better.*txt_cp1_bkg60_2_1~Hello Spider Rider. I just found out about my friend.*txt_cp1_bkg60_2_2~He's in a very bad condition.*txt_cp2_bkg7_1_1~Today is your turn to go on patrol.*txt_cp2_bkg7_1_2~I recommend you begin in the forest.*txt_cp2_bkg7_1_3~Have a safe patrol.*txt_cp2_bkg8_1_1~I saw Magma in the forest, he looked very sad.*txt_cp2_bkg10_1_1~Have a safe patrol.*txt_cp2_bkg15_1_1~Another Spider Rider just passed by. I think he went to the old school.*txt_cp2_bkg18_1_1~Leave me alone.*txt_cp2_bkg18_2_1~I don't know what you are talking about.*txt_cp2_bkg18_2_2~Where is Portia ?!*txt_cp2_bkg18_2_3~Did I do something to hurt you?*txt_cp2_bkg18_2_4~I don't believe you have lost your memory.*txt_cp2_bkg18_2_5~The light leads to knowledge.*txt_cp2_bkg18_2_6~Knowledge leads to compassion*txt_cp2_bkg18_2_7~Are you spying on me?*txt_cp2_bkg18_3_1~It's the entrance to the old school. I've never seen it before.*txt_cp2_bkg18_3_2~Let's go inside*txt_cp2_bkg18_3_3~Aquine has disappeared again*txt_cp2_bkg18_3_4~That's a bad sign.*txt_cp2_bkg47_1_1~It looks like it's going to rain. I should put away my tools. *txt_cp2_bkg47_1_2~My shovel has disappeared.*txt_cp2_bkg47_1_3~I'm losing everything today.*txt_cp2_bkg47_1_4~First my shovel and now the keys to the school.*txt_cp2_bkg47_1_5~Yes, I am the holder of the keys, but I have lost them.*txt_cp2_bkg48_1_1~We are going to watch her just the same.*txt_cp2_bkg48_1_2~That would be very surprising.*txt_cp2_bkg48_1_3~Aquine is a very special person.*txt_cp2_bkg48_1_4~I think the Oracle has given her special powers. *txt_cp2_bkg48_1_5~She is definitely up to something.*txt_cp2_bkg48_1_6~We found Aquine near the entrance of our school.*txt_cp2_bkg48_1_7~She does not remember what happened.*txt_cp2_bkg48_1_8~We will take care of her.*txt_cp2_bkg48_1_9~Follow Aquine.*txt_cp2_bkg48_1_10~It is hidden in the library, but I need the keys to open the door.*txt_cp2_bkg48_1_11~Where is this book?*txt_cp2_bkg48_1_12~There exists in this place and object that belongs to the Oracle.*txt_cp2_bkg48_1_13~It's a secret that belongs in a holy book.*txt_cp2_bkg48_1_14~They must be interested in something.*txt_cp2_bkg48_1_15~Why do the Invectids want to attack us?*txt_cp2_bkg48_1_16~We must enter the library.*txt_cp2_bkg49_1_1~Hello*txt_cp2_bkg49_1_2~Who are you?*txt_cp2_bkg49_2_1~Aquine, qui sont ces trangers ?*txt_cp2_bkg49_2_2~I don't know where Aquine is.*txt_cp2_bkg49_2_3~It looks like somebody has shifted the earth here.*txt_cp2_bkg49_3_1~Look, Spider Riders !*txt_cp2_bkg49_3_2~I really like our new friend. I don't want you to hurt her.*txt_cp2_bkg49_3_3~Did you find our friend?*txt_cp2_bkg59_1_1~This light*txt_cp2_bkg59_1_2~The Oracle is here.*txt_cp2_bkg59_1_3~It's a miracle.*txt_cp2_bkg59_1_4~The true power of the Oracle was hidden inside the book.*txt_cp2_bkg59_1_5~The light brings knowledge*txt_cp2_bkg59_1_6~And knowledge brings compassion.*txt_cp2_bkg59_2_1~Mission Completed. Congratulations !*txt_cp2_bkg59_3_1~The Light leads to knowledge*txt_cp2_bkg59_3_2~Knowledge leads to compassion...*txt_cp2_bkg59_4_1~It is too late now. You have failed*txt_cp2_bkg59_4_2~Watch Aquine carefully. She will get her hands on the Oracle's power.*txt_cp2_bkg59_4_3~The Oracle has abandoned us.*txt_cp2_bkg59_4_4~It's your fault!*txt_cp2_bkg59_4_5~You shall perish for this!*txt_cp2_bkg59_5_1~The book has saved us.*txt_cp3_bkg7_1_1~Igneous would like to speak with you.*txt_cp3_bkg8_1_1~Magma has discovered the Invectids' hideout in the mountains*txt_cp3_bkg8_1_2~Magma is certain that his spider Brutus's sister was captured by Buguese. *txt_cp3_bkg8_1_3~He is going after the Invectids to rescue her.*txt_cp3_bkg8_1_4~Corona went to lend him a hand.*txt_cp3_bkg8_1_5~But I believe that they are going to fall into a trap.*txt_cp3_bkg8_1_6~We have to hurry if we want to help them.*txt_cp3_bkg11_1_1~I sense something terrible is happening in the mountains.The Oracle is in danger.*txt_cp3_bkg12_1_1~It is quiet here. It looks like the Invectids are up to something *txt_cp3_bkg13_1_1~I believe that Lord Igneous is looking for you.*txt_cp3_bkg14_1_1~I believe that Lord Igneous is looking for you.*txt_cp3_bkg20_1_1~Gnaaa ! You again !*txt_cp3_bkg20_1_2~ I dare you to challenge my magnificent machines, Spider Rider.*txt_cp3_bkg20_2_1~Our friends are being attacked by Beerain's troops, we must help her.*txt_cp3_bkg20_2_2~I am patrolling the area. I haven't seen any Invectids come by here.*txt_cp3_bkg51_1_1~Look! There are fragments of the wall on the ground.*txt_cp3_bkg52_1_1~I don't understand why you must put your nose in our business.*txt_cp3_bkg52_1_2~But I know you will not get out of here in one piece.*txt_cp3_bkg52_2_1~The secret door is mentioned in the legend. We need the crystal key to open it.*txt_cp3_bkg52_2_2~We need to enter the temple to see what Buguese is up to*txt_cp3_bkg52_2_3~There has to be another door to this room.*txt_cp3_bkg52_3_1~Buguese and Aquine's tracks end here.*txt_cp3_bkg52_3_2~But this door is closed and I don't remember how to open it.*txt_cp3_bkg52_3_3~I think Corona knows how to open it. *txt_cp3_bkg52_3_4~Get out of my way insect!*txt_cp3_bkg52_3_5~Nothing can stop me from finding Portia.*txt_cp3_bkg52_3_6~We got rid of those pests, but we're still running late.*txt_cp3_bkg52_3_7~We need to enter the temple to see what Buguese is up to.*txt_cp3_bkg54_1_1~You got here just in time.*txt_cp3_bkg54_1_2~There is a legend about the Oracle seeking shelter in the mountains.*txt_cp3_bkg54_1_3~It mentions a crystal key that is needed to open the door.*txt_cp3_bkg54_1_4~I know where the key is, but I can't defeat the creature that is guarding it. *txt_cp3_bkg54_1_5~I can really use your help*txt_cp3_bkg54_1_6~I hear some noise outside, I think they are going to need our help.*txt_cp3_bkg54_2_1~You just found the crystal key!*txt_cp3_bkg58_1_1~You have interfered with my plans one too many times.*txt_cp3_bkg58_1_2~You will be suitably punished.*txt_cp3_bkg58_1_3~Aquine, attack!*txt_cp3_bkg58_2_1~Do not approach me, or I will have to destroy you.*txt_cp3_bkg58_3_1~Mission Completed! Congratulations.*txt_cp3_bkg58_4_1~Invectids desecrated the Oracle's temple.*txt_cp3_bkg58_4_2~We have succeeded in protecting the temple.*txt_cp3_bkg58_5_1~Aquine has a bracelet.*txt_cp3_bkg58_5_2~That was a great battle, congratulations Spider Rider.*txt_cp3_bkg58_6_1~Buguese ! Wait !*txt_cp3_bkg58_6_2~Buguese and Aquine ran away *txt_cp3_bkg58_7_1~I see you have come a long way*txt_cp3_bkg58_7_2~But the Oracle's temple will be your tomb.*txt_cp3_bkg58_7_3~Ha-ha-ha!*txt_cp3_bkg58_7_4~You are no match for me.Prepare to be destroyed.</lockitmissions>
<lockitvisual>txtLoading1~Earn Gil!*txtLoading2~Improve your Deck!*txtLoading3~Defeat the Invectids!*txtLoading4~Become a Hero!*btnNext~Next*txtUser~USERNAME:*txtPass~PASSWORD:*btnRegis~REGISTER*btnLog~LOGIN*txtConnecting~CONNECTING TO SERVER*txtConnected~CONNECTED*txtConnecFail~CONNECTION FAILED*txtWait~PLEASE WAIT*txtWait2~Please wait*txtCardOff~CARD OFFERED*txtTrade~TRADE*txtPage~PAGE*btnOffer~OFFER*btnQuit~QUIT*btnAccept~ACCEPT*btnRefuse~REFUSE*txtValue~VALUE*txtYouControl~It's your turn. Make your offer.*txtControl~is in control of the trade.|Your turn will begin  in a few seconds.*btnYes~YES*btnNo~NO*txtYour~Your*txtNotEnough~NOT ENOUGH*txtMerchant~Merchant*txtBlacksmith~blacksmith*txtCraftman~Craftman*txtTeacher~teacher*txtMerch1T~BATTLE ACTION*txtMerch2T~BOOST*txtBlacksmithT~ATTACK GEAR*txtCraftmanT~DEFENSE GEAR*txtTeacherT~SPECIAL*txtSure~Are you sure that you want to buy*btnExit~EXIT*txtQuit~DO YOU WANT|TO QUIT ?*btnOk~OK*btnCancel~CANCEL*txtTooMany~You have too many cards in your deck.*txtCardDel~Choose a card to delete*txtDiscon~disconnect*txtWin~winner*txtMiniGTitle~MINI-GAME SPIDER RIDERS*txtMiniG1~To Lumen's rescue*txtMiniG2~Spider races*txtMiniG3~The invasion*txtMiniG4~The monsters in the forest*txtMiniG5~The hunt*txtMiniG6~The Invectid's Challenge*txtMiniG7~The Duel*txtError~Error*txtStatus~STATUS*txtNames~NAMES*txtPts~POINTS*txtMiniG1Desc~Help Prince Lumen become|a better warrior*txtMiniG2Desc~Participate in the|spider races*txtMiniG3Desc~Help the peasants|by hunting insects*txtMiniG4Desc~Discover the creatures|of the forest*txtMiniG5Desc~Do you want to|gather medicinal plants*txtMiniG6Desc~Confront fearsome|Invectid fighters*btnInst~Instructions*btnHigh~High Scores*txtHigh~HIGH SCORES*btnPlayS~PLAY SINGLE*btnPlayM~PLAY MULTI*txtInst1_1~It's not easy being a prince.||You have all sorts of strenuous tasks.||Especially training.*txtInst1_2~When a number lights up, you must press on the same number on the digital keypad at the same time.  The more you press, the more I work.*txtInst1_3~But be careful, keep your eye on the clock.|Once the time is up, I'm going back to my nap.|Good luck!*txtInst2_1~Spider racing is a simple sport, but it's demanding.*txtInst2_2~You must move your spider forward with your keyboard arrows.||Make sure to avoid walls and obstacles.*txtInst2_3~Your spider needs energy to finish the race.  Don't forget to pick up reserves along the track.||Good luck.*txtInst3_1~The harvest is under attack.  You must act.  You must eliminate the hungry insects that have invaded the lofts and are eating the harvest.*txtInst3_2~Aim for the insects with the mouse and left-click to chase them away.|Be careful not to aim at peasants who are also chasing insects.*txtInst3_3~Beware of other insects that launch projectiles.  They can harm you much faster.|By touching an hourglass, you will receive a time bonus.*txtInst4_1~Forest monsters are not always dangerous.  They must be studied to be understood.*txtInst4_2~By using the mouse, click on the camera and help me take snapshots of the creatures.|You have 9 chances to take the best pictures.*txtInst4_3~Forest animals don't like to be disturbed.  You will only have a few seconds to take the picture.*txtInst4_4~By catching the hourglass, you get more time.|You can look at your photographs later in the album.|The better your photograph, the more points you will earn for your work.*txtInst5_1~Our reserves of medicinal plants needs to be replenished. Unfortunately, they only grow in regions controlled by Invectids.*txtInst5_2~Use the arrows on the keyboard to guide Flame.||Use your mouse to aim.|Left-click to shoot.*txtInst5_3~You must gather medicinal plants before Flame's energy gets to zero.||Diamonds will earn you bonuses.||Avoid enemies and projectiles.*txtInst6_1~Stag has issued a new challenge.  He has captured humans and will not release them unless I can vanquish his champion, without using any cards.*txtInst6_2~Use the keyboard|arrow keys and space bar||Punch : hit Space|Low Attack : hold Up Arrow and hit Space|Uppercut : hold Space and Release Jump Attack : hit Up Arrow(in mid air) and hit Space*txtInst6_3~Charge Attack :|Right Arrow + Right Arrow + Space|Never give up!*txtSearch~SPIDER RIDERS|is searching for an opponent*txtOppName~Your opponent's name:*txtFound~OPPONENT FOUND!*txtVicPts~VICTORY POINTS</lockitvisual>
<lockitsheets>txtCollection~CARDS IN YOUR COLLECTION*txtTipGils~Use Gils in cards shop*txtCamp~Which Bonus Level do you | want to play?*btnCamp1~Bonus 1*btnCamp2~Bonus 2*btnCamp3~Bonus 3*txtWebcode~Enter the webcode for this Bonus Level*txtSelectName~Select your character's name and appearance.*txtSaveNClick~Save, then click the Mission button to play.*txtSelectSpName~Select your spider's name and appearance.*txtSpSave~Save, then click the Mission button to go back to your adventure.*txtThrowAw~Are you sure you want to throw this card away?*txtLookCards~Click the card you want to see. Use the arrows to look at all the cards.*txtChangeGuild~Joining or changing your guild during an event means you will not be able to participate in the current event and win prizes, do you wish to continue?*txtJoinG1~Excellent, you have joined my guild. Members of my guild receive cards that will be very useful in battle.*txtJoinG2~Thanks for joining my guild. As a sign of gratitude, here are some good offensive cards for battle.*txtJoinG3~You have joined my guild in the defense of Arachna. Here are some cards that will protect you in battle.*txtJoinG4~Comrade, together we will crush our opponents. Here are some cards that you will find useful in many situations.*txtG1Desc~'s friends are fearless and determined.  They are a bit cocky and they are always ready for battle to defend a worthy cause and help their friends.*txtG2Desc~'s companions courageously fight to save Arachna. They are known for their determination when protecting the people of the inner world.*txtG3Desc~' comrades uphold order and justice in Arachna.  They always fight with honor and rely on strategy and defense to win battles.*txtG4Desc~'s allies freely roam the inner world seeking adventure.  They are powerful warriors who fear nothing and accept all challenges.*txtCharSheet~CHARACTER SHEET*btnBoy~BOY*btnGirl~GIRL*txtHair~HAIR*txtEyes~EYES*txtSkin~SKIN TONE*txtUpBody~UPPER BODY*txtLowBody~LOWER BODY*txtArmor~ARMOR*txtAtt~ATTACK DICE*txtDef~DEFENSE*txtHealth~HEALTH*txtVicPts~VICTORY PTS*txtGuildPts~GUILD PTS*btnRand~RANDOM SELECTION*btnLogout~LOGOUT*txtLogout~Do you really want to quit this game and log out?*btnSaveAva~SAVE|AVATAR*txtNotSaveChar~Are you sure you want to go back to your adventure without saving your character?*txtNotSaveSpi~Are you sure you want to go back to your adventure without saving your spider?*txtMovMissions~Are you sure you want to move on to the missions? YOU WILL LEAVE THE INNER WORLD.*btnMission~MISSION*btnInnerWorld~ARACHNA|ONLINE*btnCampaign~BONUS LEVELS*txtFirst3Lvl~You should play the first three missions before playing Arachna Online*txtJoinGuild1st~You need to join a Guild first before entering Arachna Online*txtExitMissions~Are you sure you want to exit the missions to enter the Inner World?*txtSpiSheet~SPIDER SHEET*txtDice~ATTACK DICE*txtBody~BODY*txtHead~HEAD*txtLegs~LEGS*txtName~NAME*btnSaveSpi~SAVE|SPIDER*btnMale~MALE*btnFemale~FEMALE*txtDeck~CARD SHEET: deck*btnCheck~Select*btnUncheck~Unselect*btnBasket~Delete*btnSaveDeck~SAVE DECK*txtGuild~GUILD*txtSelect~SELECT YOUR GUILD*btnDesc~DESCRIPTION*txtJoin~Join a Guild to receive cards, participate in events and win prizes*btnSolo~Solo*btnMulti~Multi Player*btnHelp~Help*btnSound~Sound*btnRider~My Rider*btnSpider~My Spider*btnCards~My Cards*btnGuild~My Guild*btnJoin~JOIN*btnEvents~EVENTS*txtMentor~Guild's mentor*txtGCards~GUILD CARDS*btnBack~BACK*txtPos~POSITION*txtAvPts~AVERAGE POINTS*txtHigh~HIGH SCORES|FOR CURRENT EVENT*txtReward~REWARD*txtEvEnd~EVENT ENDS*txtOptions~OPTIONS*btnUrChar~YOUR CHARACTER*btnArachKing~ARACHNA KINGDOM*txtInfTitle~INFORMATION BOOKLET*txtInfBook~Spider Riders Online offers you a fantastic adventure |in Arachna Kingdom. You must complete missions| and confront Invectids controlled by the evil Mantid. |Learn how to quickly become a Spider Rider by |reading up on the following subjects.*txtSheet~sheet*txtCardsDir~cards directory*txtGuilds~guilds*txtBrowsing~browsing*txtCombat~combat*txtCards~cards*txtCharStart~The character sheet is|the starting point.*txtCharSheetInf1~1 : Choose your appearance*txtCharSheetInf2~2 : Your victory points and| your rank*txtCharSheetInf3~3 : Hexagons display your| combat characteristics*txtCharSheetInf4~4 : Attack value*txtCharSheetInf5~5 : Defense value*txtCharSheetInf6~6 : Life points*txtCharSheetInf7~7 : View your spider's sheet*txtCharSheetInf8~8 : View your card directory*txtCharSheetInf9~9 : Choose your Guild*txtCharSheetInf10~10 : To save your choices,| click on "save"*txtCharSheetInf11~11 : You can then enter missions*txtCharSheetInf12~12 : Enter Arachna Online*txtCharSheetInf13~You can consult your sheet at any|time by clicking on the icon located|on the bar at the top of the screen.*btnNext~NEXT*btnPrev~PREVIOUS*txtCardDir~YOUR CARD DIRECTORY*txtCardDirDesc~The card directory contains all|the cards in your possession*txtCardDirInf1~Card listing*txtCardDirInf2~Change page*txtCardDirInf3~Number of cards in|your possession*txtCardDirInf4~Zoom on card*txtCardDirInf5~Card type*txtCardDirInf6~Card name*txtCardDirInf7~Card effect*txtCardDirInf8~Value in Gils*txtCardDirInf9~Power cards On/Off*txtCardDirInf10~Select a deck*txtCardDirInf11~Gils you receive allow you to buy cards|from shopkeepers.||You can turn Off a card if you don't wish|to use it during combat.||You can also create different decks by|combining your cards.*txtTheGuilds~THE GUILDS*txtGuildsInf1~A Guild represents a group|of players who work together in the|Arachna Kingdom.||Joining a Guild gives you special|armor and cards for your deck.||It also gives you access to events|where you can win prizes.|You can choose between 4 Guilds.*txtGuildsInf2~Guild name*txtGuildsInf3~Description*txtGuildsInf4~Guild cards*txtGuildsInf5~Window on the events of | Arachna Kingdom*txtBrowsingCap~BROWSING*txtBrowsingInf1~Moving your character||To move your character, simply click on a |square. A white square indicates where the |character will go.*txtBrowsingInf2~Arrows||When an arrow appears, it indicates a |passageway. A passageway may be blocked. |To open it, your character must either |defeat an enemy or find an object to |place in that location.*txtBrowsingInf3~Finding an object||To pick up an object, position your character |on the corresponding square. The objects |you find appear in your inventory. *txtBrowsingInf4~Inventory||To open your inventory, click on the backpack |icon located in the bar on the left at the top |of the screen. When the inventory is |open, click on the object you wish to place. |The inventory will disappear to allow you to |place the object.*txtBrowsingInf5~Placing an object||To place an object from your inventory, simply click |on the screen. Stars indicate where the placement |zones are located. When an object is placed in |the wrong spot, it is automatically sent back |to the inventory.*txtBrowsingInf6~Finding a card||During missions, you will find cards that allow you to build|your deck. They will be useful during battle. You can see|the cards you picked up in your character sheet.*txtCombatCap~COMBAT*txtTabRank~Rank*txtTabTitle~Title*txtTabHP~Health|points*txtTabVicPts~Victory|points*txtTabTrainee~Trainee*txtTabScout~Scout*txtTabRider~Rider*txtTabWarrior~Warrior*txtTabCaptain~Captain*txtTabKnight~Knight*txtTabCommandant~Commandant*txtTabCrusader~Crusader*txtTabChampion~Champion*txtTabHero~Hero*txtCombatInf1~Arachna is filled with enemies ready for combat.||To be successful in combat, you must reduce your|adversary's life points to 0. To do this, your attack|value must be higher than their defense value.||You can improve your attack by using the dice and|cards in the following way:*txtCombatInf2~Click on the "Throw the dice" button|A number of dice equal to your attack|number will roll and stop on a color. Take |the colored dice and move them over |cards of the same color. The dice will |activate the selected cards.*txtCombatInf3~Now click on the "Action" button. Your|character will attack the opponent.||An attack is successful if the attack|value is greater than the defense|value.*txtCombatInf4~Adversary's zone*txtCombatInf5~Your sheet*txtCombatInf6~Attack value*txtCombatInf7~Defense value*txtCombatInf8~Life points*txtCombatInf9~Roll the dice button*txtCombatInf10~Action button*txtCombatInf11~Your deck*txtCombatInf12~Your cards*txtCombatInf13~Trash bin*txtCombatInf14_1~A white dice is worth 0 points.*txtCombatInf14_2~A red dice increases your attack value.*txtCombatInf14_3~A yellow dice can be used on a yellow Boost card.*txtCombatInf14_4~A green dice can be used on a green Equipment card.*txtCombatInf14_5~A blue dice can be used on a blue Battle action card.*txtCombatInf15~Winning in combat will|earn you victory points.|By accumulating victory|points, you can move up|to the next rank.|By becoming stronger,|you can vanquish more|powerful enemies.*txtCardsCap~CARDS*txtCardsInf1_1~You can create up to 3 different decks for different situations.|The Spider Riders Online game offers|61 different collectible cards.*txtCardsInf1_2~They are divided into 3 categories.*txtCardsInf1_3~BOOST : Adds a bonus to your attack|EQUIPMENT : Permanent card that adds different bonuses.|BATTLE ACTION : Strategy card*txtCardsInf2~By joining a Guild, you will receive cards.|You can then collect Gils to buy other cards from|shopkeepers.The best way to find cards is to play|the missions.||You can also trade cards with other players.|To do this, click on the Trade button in the Speed|chat window.*txtCardsInf3~These cards are available throughout the game. Find'em all!*txtArachKing~ARACHNA KINGDOM*txtMissions~missions*txtMerch~merchants*txtMsg~message*txtTrading~trading*txtChallenge~challenge*txtMGames~multiplayer games*txtMissionsCap~MISSIONS*txtMissionsInf1_1~Spider Riders Online offers you|two kinds of Spider Rider adventures:|solo or in teams.*txtMissionsInf1_2~If you want to play single player, we re-|commend you play the missions. They will|show your character discovering Arachna,|dismantling the Invectid's plans by finding a|spider and finding cards, and becoming a|Spider Rider.||You can access them from your character|sheet.*txtMissionsInf2~If you think you are ready to play with a|team, you can enter Arachna Kingdom.|It is a vast universe filled with lots of|enemies and adventures.||There you will meet the characters|from the animated series and help|combat the Invectids that are trying to|conquer Arachna.*txtMerchantsCap~MERCHANTS*txtMerchantsInf1~In the world of Arachna, you will find different|enemies and mini-games. Upon completing a|mini-game or defeating an enemy, you will|receive Gils. You can then visit shopkeepers|and buy cards with your Gils.||This may improve your deck and make you|stronger in combat. But beware! The more|powerful a card is, the more expensive it is.||You will find shopkeepers in the city, in the|village and in the school.*txtMsgCap~MESSAGES*txtInfo~information*txtDictionary~dictionary*txtDictionaryCap~DICTIONARY*txtMsgInf1~To display messages:||1. Launch the communication console|by clicking the dialog bubble.|2. Type the first letters of your message.|3. A list of available words is displayed,|to view more words use the scroll bar or|arrow key to go through the list. Select a|word by clicking it with your mouse or by|using the arrows on your  keyboard;|send the message by pressing ENTER.|The word is automatically displayed in|the message box.|4. When you've finished your message,|click OK to send it.*txtTrades~TRADES*txtTradingInf1~It's easy to trade cards with other players:||1. Launch the communication|console by clicking on the dialog|bubble.|2. Select the trade icon and click OK.||The trade button appears above your|avatar.*txtTradingInf2~If a player clicks this icon, the trading|window will open and you can:||1.  Select the cards you want to trade.|2. Select the cards you want from the|other player.|3. Click the OFFER button to launch|the trade.|4. The other player then clicks to ACCEPT|or OFFER to offer something else.*txtChallengeCap~CHALLENGE*txtChallengeInf1~You can also issue a challenge to|another player:||1. Launch the communication|console by clicking the dialog bubble.|2. Select the card combat icon and| click OK.||The challenge icon appears above your|avatar. If a player clicks this icon, the|combat system window will open and|you face each other in a duel.*txtChallengeInf2~New combat rules for duel mode:||- Players have a time limit for|throwing the dice and playing their|cards.||- When a player cannot draw| anymore cards they automatically lose| the combat.*txtMGamesCap~MULTIPLAYER GAMES*txtMGamesInf1~To play games in multiplayer mode,|propose a new game as follows:||1. Launch the communication|console by clicking the dialog|bubble.|2. Select the icon for the mini-game|you want to play and click OK.||The mini-game icon appears above|your avatar. If a player clicks this icon,|the game window will open and you|can play together.*txtUser~ENTER YOUR DESIRED USERNAME:*txtPass~ENTER YOUR DESIRED PASSWORD:*txtPassConfirm~PLEASE CONFIRM YOUR PASSWORD:*txtFanClub~Join the Fan Club and receive stuff*txtAge~HOW OLD ARE YOU?:</lockitsheets>
<lockitworld>info_ev1_collect_1~The Invectids have destroyed the bridge!*info_ev1_collect_2~The woodsman must rebuild the bridge.*info_ev1_collect_3~The path between the village and city is blocked.*info_ev1_collect_4~Help the peasants to rebuild the bridge.*info_ev1_collect_5~The path between the village and city is blocked.*info_ev1_sprint_1~The woodsman has almost completed the bridge.*info_ev1_sprint_2~Last chance to help rebuild the bridge.*info_ev1_sprint_3~Help your Guild rebuild the bridge to win the reward.*info_ev1_result_1~The bridge is rebuilt. Congratulations to all Spider Riders!*info_ev1_result_2~Members of *info_ev1_result_3~ receive 200 Gils for the bridge repairs.*info_ev1_result_4~The bridge is open.*info_ev2_collect_1~The Invectids have taken prisoners.*info_ev2_collect_2~Mantid has moved his soldiers.*info_ev2_collect_3~Igneous needs help to save the prisoners.*info_ev2_collect_4~Calling all Guilds. The prisoners must be freed.*info_ev2_collect_5~New offensive by Invectid troops.*info_ev2_sprint_1~The Invectid's still have prisoners.*info_ev2_sprint_2~Last chance to free the prisoners.*info_ev2_sprint_3~Your Guild needs you to vanquish the Invectids.*info_ev2_result_1~All the prisoners are free. Congratulations to all Spider Riders!*info_ev2_result_2~Members of *info_ev2_result_3~ receive 3 cards for their courage.*info_ev2_result_4~The Invectids have been defeated.*info_ev3_collect_1~Lumen needs your help to train.*info_ev3_collect_2~You must help me.*info_ev3_collect_3~The Prince's training isn't going well.*info_ev3_collect_4~Play the castle game and help your Guild.*info_ev3_collect_5~Meet in the hall for the newest event.*info_ev3_sprint_1~When will this training end?*info_ev3_sprint_2~My vacation is coming soon.*info_ev3_sprint_3~Come and give me a hand in the hall.*info_ev3_result_1~Thanks to all those who helped me.*info_ev3_result_2~Members of *info_ev3_result_3~ Guild receive 150 Gils for helping the Prince.*info_ev3_result_4~I can finally take my vacation.*info_ev4_collect_1~Sparkle is waiting for you in the hall.*info_ev4_collect_2~The Princess is preparing for Oracle's celebration.*info_ev4_collect_3~The big event will begin soon.*info_ev4_collect_4~It's glowing rock season in the inner world.*info_ev4_collect_5~Princess Sparkle needs your help.*info_ev4_sprint_1~Oracle's celebration will soon take place.*info_ev4_sprint_2~This is your last chance to help Princess Sparkle.*info_ev4_sprint_3~There are still a few stones missing for the hall's decorations.*info_ev4_result_1~Congratulations to all Spider Riders!*info_ev4_result_2~Members of *info_ev4_result_3~'s Guild receive the Positive Attitude card.*info_ev4_result_4~Oracle's celebration was amazing!*info_ev5_collect_1~Corona needs help.*info_ev5_collect_2~Grasshop is preparing a new attack.*info_ev5_collect_3~Attention all Spider Riders. The city is in danger.*info_ev5_collect_4~Attack Grasshop's infernal machine.*info_ev5_collect_5~The blacksmith needs new pieces.*info_ev5_sprint_1~Grasshop is trying to rebuild his machine.*info_ev5_sprint_2~Come help me.*info_ev5_sprint_3~Help your Guild by dismantling the infernal machine.*info_ev5_result_1~Congratulations to all Spider Riders!*info_ev5_result_2~Members of *info_ev5_result_3~ receive 120 points for defeating Grasshop.*info_ev5_result_4~The city is out of danger.*info_ev6_collect_1~The city has been hit with an epidemic.*info_ev6_collect_2~The Healer needs your help.*info_ev6_collect_3~Our medicine reserves are empty.*info_ev6_collect_4~I shall exterminate the humans!*info_ev6_collect_5~Attention all Guilds. We must find medicinal plants.*info_ev6_sprint_1~The epidemic is spreading through the city.*info_ev6_sprint_2~We will never overcome this disease.*info_ev6_sprint_3~I beg you, please help us.*info_ev6_result_1~Congratulations to all Spider Riders!*info_ev6_result_2~Members of *info_ev6_result_3~'s Guild receive the Sanctuary card for having saved the city.*info_ev6_result_4~The epidemic has been halted.*info_ev7_collect_1~Help the villagers gather the harvest.*info_ev7_collect_2~We must gather our harvest.*info_ev7_collect_3~The shopkeeper is expecting you in the village for a new mission.*info_ev7_collect_4~Harvesting is much faster with a spider.*info_ev7_collect_5~It's harvest time in the village.*info_ev7_sprint_1~The shopkeeper's reserves are not full yet.*info_ev7_sprint_2~Last chance to help the villagers.*info_ev7_sprint_3~Help your Guild by gathering lots of crops.*info_ev7_result_1~Congratulations to all Spider Riders!*info_ev7_result_2~Members of *info_ev7_result_3~ receive 200 Gils for the harvested crops.*info_ev7_result_4~The shopkeeper's lofts are full.*info_ev8_collect_1~We will exterminate you.*info_ev8_collect_2~Aquine is invading the city.*info_ev8_collect_3~We will not allow the Invectids to destroy our homes.*info_ev8_collect_4~Attack the Invectids that have invaded the city.*info_ev8_collect_5~Aquine's offensive on the city has begun.*info_ev8_sprint_1~Aquine has launched a counter-attack.  Everyone to the city!*info_ev8_sprint_2~The Invectids are swarming the city.*info_ev8_sprint_3~Spider Rider, Aquine must be defeated!*info_ev8_result_1~The Invectids have been chased away.  Congratulations to all Spider Riders!*info_ev8_result_2~Members of *info_ev8_result_3~'s Guild receive 180 points for the city's victory.*info_ev8_result_4~The city is now out of danger.*info_ev9_collect_1~Competition to determine the Guild with the best racers.*info_ev9_collect_2~A racing championship, awesome!*info_ev9_collect_3~Spider Riders can register for the racing championship.*info_ev9_collect_4~Compete in the spider races to help your Guild win.*info_ev9_collect_5~Meet in the city for the racing championship.*info_ev9_sprint_1~There's not much time left to register for the races.*info_ev9_sprint_2~Help your Guild triumph in the racing championship.*info_ev9_sprint_3~I am the best racer.*info_ev9_result_1~The championship is over. Congratulations to all Spider Riders!*info_ev9_result_2~Members of *info_ev9_result_3~ receive 150 Gils for the races.*info_ev9_result_4~The racing championship is over.*info_ev10_collect_1~I declare the Guild Competition is open.*info_ev10_collect_2~Find the hidden flags to win the special prize.*info_ev10_collect_3~We will win the Guild Competition.*info_ev10_collect_4~The chamberlain is expecting your flags for the Guild Competition.*info_ev10_collect_5~To all my Spider Rider friends, don't forget the Guild Competition.*info_ev10_sprint_1~Give it your best shot and join the Guild Competition.*info_ev10_sprint_2~The contest will soon be over.*info_ev10_sprint_3~A maximum of flags is needed.*info_ev10_result_1~The Guild competition is over.*info_ev10_result_2~Members of *info_ev10_result_3~'s Guild receive the Cutie Pie card as a prize.*info_ev10_result_4~Prince Lumen has declared the end of the Guild Competition.*info_ev11_collect_1~The city's children have received some very strange toys.*info_ev11_collect_2~Free the city's inhabitants.*info_ev11_collect_3~I have a diabolical plan.*info_ev11_collect_4~Help!*info_ev11_collect_5~Something terrible is happening.*info_ev11_sprint_1~There are still some prisoners.*info_ev11_sprint_2~Liberate the prisoners and help your Guild..*info_ev11_sprint_3~Time is running out! The inhabitants must be liberated.*info_ev11_result_1~The inhabitants are saved. Congratulations to all Spider Riders!*info_ev11_result_2~Members of *info_ev11_result_3~ receive the False Order and Trap cards.*info_ev11_result_4~Grasshop's plans have been foiled.*info_ev12_collect_1~The Spiders Riders will be powerless this time.*info_ev12_collect_2~Stag has captured the school children.*info_ev12_collect_3~Invectids have challenged the Spider Riders in the marshes.*info_ev12_collect_4~Stag has taken prisoners.*info_ev12_collect_5~Battle the Invectids battle to help make your Guild win.*info_ev12_sprint_1~Stag's challenge will soon be over.*info_ev12_sprint_2~The children captured by Stag must be helped.*info_ev12_sprint_3~You're not strong enough to vanquish my champion.*info_ev12_result_1~Stag's challenge is over. Congratulations to all Spider Riders!*info_ev12_result_2~Members of *info_ev12_result_3~ receive 180 points for their participation.*info_ev12_result_4~Stag's prisoners are free.*info_invPlain_1~The plains and the village are secured.*info_invPlain_2~Invectid troops are crossing the plain.*info_invPlain_3~Grasshop has surrounded the village.*info_invPlain_4~Beware! The Invectids have invaded the plains and the village.*info_invForest_1~The forest is peaceful.*info_invForest_2~Invectids have been seen in the forest.*info_invForest_3~Beerain is trying to invade the forest.*info_invForest_4~You must free the forest from Beerain's claws!*info_invMountain_1~We have chased the Invectids out of the mountains.*info_invMountain_2~Some Invectids are hiding in the mountains.*info_invMountain_3~Aquine has moved her troops into the mountain.*info_invMountain_4~Aquine's troops are occupying the mountain..*info_invMarshe_1~The shadow has been chased from the marshes.*info_invMarshe_2~The Invectids have returned to the marshes.*info_invMarshe_3~Stag's soldiers are in the marshes and in position.*info_invMarshe_4~Stag has complete control of the marshes.*txt0100p1~A great Spider Riders needs to have powerful card in their deck.*txt0100p2~You can find a list of cards in the help menu.*txt0100p3~The Prince can use your help in the throne room.*txt0101p1~Spider Riders gain experience by entering battles*txt0101p2~Experience points from combat help you move up levels.*txt0101p3~You must move up eleven levels to become a hero.*txt0102p1~You gain experience points by battling monsters.*txt0102p2~There are tougher opponents in the swamps.*txt0102p3~There are two types of opponents. Monsters and opponents with a deck of cards.*txt0103p1~shopkeepers sell cards that you can use to improve your deck*txt0103p2~You can buy gils at the shopkeeper, but you need to have gils*txt0103p3~You can win gils by playing the mini-games*txt0104p1~You can win gils by playing the mini-games*txt0104p2~There are six mini-games in Arachna*txt0104p3~By helping Prince Lumen train you can win gils*txt0105p1~Boost cards are not expensive and can do alot of damage*txt0105p2~Equipment cards can make you more powerful*txt0105p3~Battle Action cards have special powers, you need to learn to use them properly*txt0106p1~Play the missions to learn about Arachna and to learn about being a Spider Riders.*txt0106p2~You can get your very own spider by completing mission five*txt0106p3~Play all 15 missions and receive cards to improve your deck*txt0107p1~Train yourself by dueling with other Spider Riders*txt0107p2~Click on the icon above other Spider Riders to accept their challenge*txt0107p3~Open the Communications Console to use the multiplayer functions*txt0108p1~Defeat the Invectids in battle to chase them out of the city*txt0108p2~The further you are from the city, the tougher the opponents *txt0108p3~The tougher the opponent, the greater the reward*txt0109p1~The blacksmith can create very good weapons*txt0109p2~If you need protection, go see the craftsman*txt0109p3~The shopkeeper in the city sells Boost cards*txt0110p1~The blacksmith can create very good weapons*txt0110p2~If you need protection, go see the craftsman*txt0110p3~The shopkeeper in the city sells Boost cards*txt0111p1~I can use your help in the throne room*txt0111p2~There are five different places where you can buy cards in Arachna*txt0111p3~Use the communication console to access the multiplayer functions*txt0112p1~I'm in great shape today.  Are you ready for a combat?*txt0113p1~I don't think a little training would do any harm. What do you say?*txt0114p1~Show me a little bit of what you've got.*txt0200p1~Its a good idea to have lots of different cards in your deck*txt0200p2~Boost cards are very inexpensive and can do lots of damage*txt0200p3~Use the Disarm card to remove cards from your opponent in battle*txt0201p1~A well balanced deck can help you in battle*txt0201p2~Defeat the Invectids to gain more experience*txt0201p3~Mantid and his generals want to take over Arachna*txt0202p1~One day, when I'll be a Spider Rider, I'm going to have a powerful deck.*txt0202p2~You can buy Boost card from the shopkeeper in the city.*txt0202p3~You can play lots of different games with the communications console*txt0203p1~Battle Action cards can be very useful in combat*txt0203p2~The teacher has some mysterious cards*txt0203p3~You can challenge your friends in mini-games with the communications console*txt0204p1~A good deck has a mix of Boost, Equipment and Battle Action cards.*txt0204p2~The tougher the opponent, the greater the reward*txt0204p3~The number that appears above some monsters head represents the number of monsters that must be defeated*txt0205p1~Equipment cards can make you more powerful*txt0205p2~Battle Action cards are more useful against opponents with decks*txt0205p3~Battle Action cards can increase your life points*txt0206p1~I have won lots of gil by participating in the spider races*txt0206p2~We know so little about the creatures in the forest, will you help us learn more about them by playing the picture taking game?*txt0206p3~Can you help Igneous by challenging the Invectids in the mountains?*txt0207p1~Stag believes that humans are no match for his Champion, that's why he has setup a challenge in the swamp*txt0207p2~Play the bug hunting mini-game to help the villagers protect their crops from the Invectids.*txt0207p3~Prince Lumen can use your help to train in the throne room.*txt0208p1~Can you help Igneous battle the Invectids in the mountains?*txt0208p2~Challenge Stag's champion by playing the Invectids Challenge mini-game in the swamp.*txt0208p3~I really enjoy taking part in the spider races.*txt0209p1~Each battle action card has a different affect*txt0209p2~You can get a spider of your own by playing the missions.*txt0209p3~You can look through all the cards in the help section*txt0210p1~Click on the card section of your character sheet to review your cards*txt0210p2~Deactivate cards in your deck by clicking on the check mark*txt0210p3~You can setup 3 different cards to use against different types of opponents.*txt0211p1~By combining your attack cards and the Weapon Master card, you can temporarily increase the damage you do*txt0211p2~By combining your defensive cards and the Shield Master card you can temporarily increase your defenses*txt0211p3~Some Battle Action cards are only useful against opponents with cards.*txt0212p1~The blacksmith creates some powerful weapons*txt0212p2~The letter that appears in the interface is related to the deck of cards in your character sheet*txt0212p3~The teacher has some mysterious cards he can sell you.*txt0213p1~If you need protection, go see the craftsman*txt0213p2~The shopkeeper in the city has Boost cards*txt0213p3~I think that the blacksmith is working on some weapons*txt0214p1~There are several places where you can get cards in the city*txt0214p2~You can win lots of gil against more powerful opponents*txt0214p3~By participating in events you can win rare cards.*txt0215p1~Can you help Igneous by playing the The Hunt mini-game in the mountains?*txt0215p2~You should go defeat Stag's champion by playing the Invectids Challenge mini-game in the swamp*txt0215p3~I love watching the spider races just in front of the fortress*txt0216p1~You can play lots of different games with other players through the communications console*txt0216p2~You can trade cards with the communication console*txt0216p3~Challenge other Spider Riders to a duel with the communication console*txt0217p1~There are 3 types of Equipment cards : weapons, armor and objects*txt0217p2~The Lightning Bolt card removes all the cards in play*txt0217p3~Some cards are only available by defeating powerful monsters.*txt0218p1~The shopkeeper in the village has lots of interesting cards for sale.*txt0218p2~I am going to the blacksmith shop to see his equipment cards*txt0218p3~I really enjoy going to the spider races.*txt0219p1~Prince Lumen does not like working hard, but he needs to keep up with his training in the throne room*txt0219p2~I think that the shopkeepers have new items for sale*txt0219p3~There are lots of things to do in Arachna, if you take the time to explore*txt0220p1~Only high level Spider Riders can protect us from the Invectids*txt0220p2~The people in the village say that the insects are destroying their crops, can you help them by playing the Invasion mini-game in the village?*txt0220p3~We know so little about the creatures in the forest, can you help us learn more?txt0221p1~Venus and I need to do some training. Let's go to the arena*txt0222p1~Why don't you try yourself against me in a real combat?*txt0223p1~Show me what you can do.*txt0300p1~It's a pleasure to meet you.*txt0300p2~I'm going to the village to visit my friends.*txt0300p3~The peasants are harvesting. They need some help.*txt0301p1~Hello.*txt0301p2~Grasshop is watching this region.*txt0301p3~We must beware of the Invectids or else we will lose ground.*txt0302p1~All hail the Spider Riders!*txt0302p2~We must keep our positions.*txt0302p3~The forest is crawling with strange creatures.*txt0303p1~Look out.*txt0303p2~Igneous went patrolling on the mountain side.*txt0303p3~The Invectids are preparing an attack.*txt0304p1~Greetings Spider Rider.*txt0304p2~The villagers need help with their harvest.*txt0304p3~You can help me by gathering plants from the mountains.*txt0305p1~This region is dangerous.*txt0305p2~We must push the enemy away from our walls.*txt0305p3~The humans are in danger.*txt0306p1~Hello!*txt0306p2~The marvels of the inner world must be protected from evil creatures.*txt0306p3~You must resist the Invectids.*txt0307p1~Hello young warrior.*txt0307p2~Corona and I are going on patrol.*txt0307p3~People seem really busy in the village.*txt0319p1~Do you really think you can defeat me?*txt0320p1~Why don't you try yourself against me in a real combat?*txt0321p1~Show me a little bit vectids?*txt0322p1~Don't come any closer, or I'll attack you.*txt0323p1~Get out of here or I'll crush you!*txt0324p1~Hello.*txt0324p2~Magma is looking for information about Portia.*txt0324p3~The village must be protected from the Invectids.*txt0325p1~I am happy to see you again.*txt0325p2~The peasants are harvesting. They need some help.*txt0325p3~Do you know all the animals of the forest?*txt0326p1~A Spider Rider!*txt0326p2~One day, I'll be a Spider Rider just like you!*txt0326p3~Can I see your cards?*txt0327p1~Mommy says I shouldn't talk to strangers.*txt0327p2~I am picking vegetables for lunch.*txt0327p3~I am afraid of the Invectids.*txt0328p1~May the Oracle watch over you, noble warrior.*txt0328p2~The Invectids are threatening our village.*txt0328p3~Plants must be gathered from the mountains. But it's very dangerous.*txt0329p1~Are you coming on patrol with me?*txt0329p2~It is difficult to protect the village from Invectids.*txt0329p3~You must be careful when walking through the forest. But if you can take pictures of the forest animals, you can earn a few Gils.*txt0330p1~Hello.*txt0330p2~I hope it's a good harvest.*txt0330p3~If you help us with the harvest, you will be rewarded.*txt0331p1~Hello.*txt0331p2~Prince Lumen should negotiate a truce with our enemies.*txt0331p3~The marshes are extremely dangerous.*txt0332p1~It's a dark day.*txt0332p2~We are living in difficult times.*txt0332p3~Good thing the Spider Riders are here to protect us.*txt0333p1~I am here for school supplies.*txt0333p2~The teacher has many powerful cards.*txt0333p3~The Invectids' hive rises from the marshes.*txt0334p1~The Invectids are moving towards the village.*txt0334p2~The harvest must be protected.*txt0334p3~I'm afraid that we won't be able to stop Mantid's armies.*txt0335p1~Hello.*txt0335p2~We must remain vigilant.*txt0335p3~The forest is full of danger.*txt0336p1~Hello.*txt0336p2~It's a beautiful day.*txt0336p3~The shopkeeper can sell you some cards.*txt0337p1~May the Oracle watch over you.*txt0337p2~Did you defeat the Invectids?*txt0337p3~Did you know that some opponents will give you a card if you defeat them?*txt0343p1~Show me what you can do.*txt0344p1~I'm here to teach you a lesson.*txt0345p1~Don't come any closer, or I'll attack you.*txt0346p1~Give me your crops and I won't hurt you.*txt0400p1~What are you doing here?*txt0400p2~Magma is looking for information on Portia.*txt0400p3~This forest is not very safe.*txt0401p1~Greetings Spider Rider.*txt0401p2~Not all the forest creatures are bad. The trick is to recognize them.*txt0401p3~The woodsman asked me to bring him some provisions.*txt0402p1~I like the forests of the inner world. Don't you?*txt0402p2~This is a veritable Invectid nest.*txt0402p3~I know that we can buy cards in an old school.*txt0403p1~I think I'm lost.*txt0403p2~The Invectids are invading the forest.*txt0403p3~I must get back to school.*txt0404p1~Greetings young Spider Rider.*txt0404p2~You must know how to defend yourself around here.*txt0404p3~You can earn Gils by cataloging the creatures in the forest.*txt0423p1~My master would be most displeased if you were to ruin his plans.*txt0424p1~This forest is mine!*txt0425p1~I'm going to teach you the lesson you deserve!*txt0427p1~What are you doing here?*txt0427p2~Magma is looking for information on Portia.*txt0427p3~This forest is not very safe.*txt0428p1~Did you come to visit the school?*txt0428p2~This school takes in lost children.*txt0428p3~The teacher has a great collection of objects.*txt0429p1~I must do my homework.*txt0429p2~Our teacher is receiving visitors.*txt0429p3~My parents will be picking me up soon.*txt0430p1~Are you a real Spider Rider?*txt0430p2~Do you want to play with me?*txt0430p3~The school is very close to the marshes.*txt0431p1~Spider Riders' here!*txt0431p2~I have been found out!*txt0431p3~I must warn Mantid.*txt0432p1~It's a very old school.*txt0432p2~I believe there are some interesting items to buy here.*txt0432p3~I don't like being this close to the marshes.*txt0433p1~Welcome stranger.*txt0433p2~It is a pleasure to offer you our hospitality.*txt0433p3~This school could really use your protection.*txt0449p1~My master would be most displeased if you were to ruin his plans.*txt0450p1~This place is mine!*txt0451p1~Resistance is futile. You are no match for me.*txt0500p1~We need your help to overcome the Invectids.*txt0500p2~Arachna Power!  Let's show them what we can do.*txt0500p3~Were you able to make the Invectids retreat?*txt0501p1~We need you here.*txt0501p2~It would be wiser to retreat back to Arachna.*txt0501p3~Aquine is trying to make headway with his Invectids.*txt0522p1~My master will be most pleased that I have eliminated you!*txt0523p1~Don't come any closer, or I'll attack you!*txt0524p1~Resistance is futile. You strength is no match for me.*txt0600p1~I don't like this place.*txt0600p2~Do you think Portia is here?*txt0600p3~The Invectids think they are the strongest. They are offering a reward to the one who can vanquish their champion in solo combat.*txt0601p1~Spider Riders, here!*txt0601p2~I have been found out!*txt0601p3~I must warn Mantid.*txt0602p1~Let's not stay here.*txt0602p2~Stag is challenging us again. He is offering a reward to the one who can vanquish an Invectid in solo combat.*txt0602p3~We are too close to Mantid's lair. It's not safe.*txt0617p1~My master does not want you here.*txt0618p1~You again! The Spider Riders have gone too far this time.*txt0619p1~You will be punished for your insolence!*txt0620p1~My master will be pleased to have prisoners.*txt0621p1~You are on our lands. You will learn our laws.*areaNmField~The Field*areaNmVillage~The Village*areaNmForest~The Forest*areaNmMountains~The Mountains*areaNmCity~The City*areaNmFortress~The Fortress*areaNmSwamp~The Swamp*areaNmSchool~The School*areaNmMarsh~The Marsh*txtInv~INVENTORY*txtSave~Your profile has been saved.*btnSave~Save*btnDeck~Deck*btnInv~Inventory*btnMenu~Main Menu*btnChat~Chat*txtMiniG1~Do you want to help Prince Lumen?*txtMiniG2~Do you want to participate in the spider races?*txtMiniG3~Do you want to help the peasants by hunting insects?*txtMiniG4~Do you want to discover the creatures of the forest?*txtMiniG5~Do you want to gather medicinal plants?*txtMiniG6~Do you want to confront fearsome Invectid fighters?*txtChallenge~Do you want to challenge this opponent?*txtFight~Do you want to fight this enemy?*txt_merchant_bkg23_1~Welcome young Spider Rider. I have everything you need*txt_merchant_bkg23_2~Sorry we are closed!*txt_merchant_bkg40_1~Welcome to my shop. I have all sorts of useful things for you.|Do you want to see them?*txt_merchant_bkg40_2~Sorry we are closed!*txt_merchant_bkg44_1~You may enter my shop. I make armor and protective shields.*txt_merchant_bkg44_2~Sorry we are closed!*txt_merchant_bkg45_1~Welcome young warrior. I make all sorts of weapons.*txt_merchant_bkg45_2~Sorry we are closed!*txt_merchant_bkg50_1~In this school, we study the teachings of the Oracle. With them we learn how make precious objects.*txt_merchant_bkg50_2~Sorry we are closed!*txt_ev_give1~Congratulations! You have earned *txt_ev_give2~ points for your Guild.*txt_ev_collect1~You rescued *txt_ev_collect2~|They have been added to your inventory.*txt_ev1_bkg8_closePath~The bridge is under construction! Find another way!*txt_ev1_bkg10_1~Thank you! With this wood, I can keep working.*txt_ev1_bkg10_2~I must rebuild the bridge.*txt_ev1_bkg10_3~But I don't have enough wood.*txt_ev1_bkg10_4~The bridge is coming along nicely, but I still need lots of wood.*txt_ev1_bkg10_5~I'm very happy to have finished working on the bridge.*txt_ev1_bkg12_1~What will we do?*txt_ev1_bkg12_2~If the bridge is broken, we can't transport our supplies and goods.*txt_ev1_bkg12_3~The woodsman is very courageous*txt_ev1_bkg12_4~But can he finish the bridge in time for the harvest?*txt_ev1_bkg12_5~We can now cross the bridge.*txt_ev1_bkg13_1~The Spider Riders really helped us.*txt_ev1_bkg13_2~The people of the village have rewarded us for helping them rebuild the bridge.*txt_ev1_bkg13_3~The village has decided to give a reward to the Guild that most helps the woodsman.*txt_ev1_bkg24_1~We have work to do.*txt_ev1_bkg24_2~The Invectids have destroyed the bridge. To rebuild it, we must find wood.*txt_ev1_bkg24_3~If you find some, bring it to the woodsman.*txt_ev1_bkg24_4~Also, there will be a reward for the Guild that helps him the most.*txt_ev1_bkg24_5~The woodsman works fast. We must get him some wood.*txt_ev1_bkg26_1~Poor villagers.*txt_ev1_bkg26_2~The Invectids have attacked and destroyed their bridge.*txt_ev1_bkg26_3~I know the woodsman is trying to rebuild it, but he doesn't have enough wood.*txt_ev1_bkg26_4~Can we help them?*txt_ev1_bkg26_5~Construction on the bridge has already begun, but they still need your help to gather logs.*txt_ev1_bkg26_6~The Invectids can destroy whatever they, but we will always have the strength to rebuild.*txt_ev2_item~ prisoners.*txt_ev2_bkg7_1~You saved some humans. Your courage is commendable.*txt_ev2_bkg7_2~The Invectids have captured prisoners in every region.*txt_ev2_bkg7_3~Go liberate the humans.*txt_ev2_bkg7_4~We need your help to protect them.*txt_ev2_bkg7_5~There remain many prisoners and night is approaching.*txt_ev2_bkg7_6~All the prisoners are safe.*txt_ev2_bkg12_1~I heard the Invectids attacked another village and took many prisoners.*txt_ev2_bkg12_2~We must give shelter to the Invectids' prisoners in the fortress.*txt_ev2_bkg12_3~The prisoners have been rescued. I will go see if there are any injuries.*txt_ev2_bkg18_1~The Invectids are agitated.*txt_ev2_bkg18_2~Go quickly to rescue the Invectids' human prisoners.*txt_ev2_bkg18_3~The Spider Riders have succeeded in freeing the Invectid's human prisoners.*txt_ev2_bkg26_1~Flee to the mountains.*txt_ev2_bkg26_2~The Invectids have attacked a village and taken many prisoners.*txt_ev2_bkg26_3~Mantid's soldiers are still holding human prisoners.*txt_ev2_bkg26_4~The Spider Riders have rescued the prisoners. Mantid's plan has failed.*txt_ev3_bkg26_1~My brother must go through an intensive training this week.*txt_ev3_bkg26_2~But I don't think he's very happy about it.*txt_ev3_bkg26_3~Can you help him?*txt_ev3_bkg26_4~Do you know if my brother's training is progressing?*txt_ev3_bkg26_5~The week's end is drawing near.*txt_ev3_bkg26_6~We must hurry.*txt_ev3_bkg26_7~Thanks to you, Lumen has completed the challenges.*txt_ev3_bkg28_1~You have helped the Prince! Thank you very much.*txt_ev3_bkg28_2~Tradition dictates that the Prince must soon undertake a challenge in combat.*txt_ev3_bkg28_3~I don't know how to motivate the Prince to train and prepare for this important event.*txt_ev3_bkg28_4~Nevertheless, he must be in the hall.*txt_ev3_bkg28_5~Our Prince has masterfully completed the challenges.*txt_ev3_bkg28_6~I can concern myself with other things now.*txt_ev3_bkg31_1~I think that our Prince needs our help in the hall.*txt_ev3_bkg31_2~He must succeed in an important challenge as part of his training as warrior.*txt_ev3_bkg31_3~If you help Prince Lumen, you must tell the chamberlain afterwards.*txt_ev3_bkg31_4~The date of challenge is approaching and I don't know if my Prince has completed his training.*txt_ev3_bkg31_5~The Prince has completed the challenges with the help of all our Spider Rider friends.*txt_ev3_bkg34_1~I know very well that I have to finish my training.*txt_ev3_bkg34_2~But it's so nice out today*txt_ev3_bkg34_3~I still have time to train. The week isn't over yet.*txt_ev3_bkg34_4~I have given a reward to the warriors who have most helped me.*txt_ev3_bkg34_5~This week has exhausted me. I am going to take a nap.*txt_ev3_bkg34_6~See you later.*txt_ev4_bkg7_1~The Princess is preparing a celebration in honor of the Oracle.*txt_ev4_bkg7_2~While I'm on patrol, I'll try to find gleaming stones to decorate the hall.*txt_ev4_bkg7_3~I'm back from my patrol.*txt_ev4_bkg7_4~I fought against two monsters, six Invectids and Beerain*txt_ev4_bkg7_5~But I didn't see a single gleaming stone for Sparkle.*txt_ev4_bkg13_1~Princess Sparkle has commissioned me to bring her gleaming stones.*txt_ev4_bkg13_2~I came to the village to buy some magic stones, but there aren't any for sale.*txt_ev4_bkg13_3~I'm going to bring back magical stones for the Princess to help decorate the hall.*txt_ev4_bkg13_4~But I don't see any stone anywhere.*txt_ev4_bkg13_5~Help me, quick!*txt_ev4_bkg28_1~My sister is preparing a great celebration in the hall.*txt_ev4_bkg30_1_1~Thank you for these wonderful stones.*txt_ev4_bkg30_1_2~Can you bring me more?*txt_ev4_bkg30_1_3~Friends, the celebration of the Oracle will soon begin.*txt_ev4_bkg30_1_4~Our hall must be decorated for this special occasion.*txt_ev4_bkg30_1_5~I will need as many gleaming stones as you can find.*txt_ev4_bkg30_1_6~The celebration is about to begin.*txt_ev4_bkg30_1_7~And we need more glowing rocks.*txt_ev4_bkg30_1_8~Thank you my friends.*txt_ev4_bkg30_1_9~Thanks to you and the Spider Riders, we will celebrate.*txt_ev4_bkg30_2_1~Where did all these magic stones come from?*txt_ev4_bkg30_3_1~The Oracle is most honored.*txt_ev4_bkg30_4_1~Thank you to my sister and to all those who helped her.*txt_ev4_bkg30_4_2~May the celebration of the Oracle begin.*txt_ev4_bkg42_closePath~We are decorating the hall for the celebration of the Oracle. Find another way!*txt_ev5_item~ machine pieces.*txt_ev5_bkg7_1~Ha-ha-ha!*txt_ev5_bkg7_2~Soon, my new toy will be ready.*txt_ev5_bkg7_3~And with all my soldiers, no Spider Rider will get in my way.*txt_ev5_bkg7_4~You can try to vanquish us, but you're wasting your time.*txt_ev5_bkg7_5~I will destroy this city.*txt_ev5_bkg8_1_1~Grasshop has been defeated once again.*txt_ev5_bkg8_2_1~Thank you Spider Riders for destroying the machine.*txt_ev5_bkg10_1~Where did all these Invectids come from?  We must overpower them.*txt_ev5_bkg10_2~The Invectid machine threatens the city.*txt_ev5_bkg24_1~Grasshop is building a battering ram to destroy the walls of Arachna.*txt_ev5_bkg24_2~We must destroy it and ask the blacksmith to take it apart.*txt_ev5_bkg26_1~Thanks. I'll get to work immediately.*txt_ev5_bkg26_2~I'm waiting for gears from the Invectid's machine so I can take them apart.*txt_ev5_bkg26_3~I don't think there are any gears left to take apart. I will get back to my work.*txt_ev5_bkg28_1~Look out! The Invectids are at the city's gates.*txt_ev5_bkg28_2~The Invectids have almost finished building a gigantic weapon.*txt_ev5_bkg28_3~The Invectid machine made to destroy the city has been demolished.*txt_ev6_bkg7_1~My master has ordered me to spread a disease in the city.*txt_ev6_bkg7_2~Surrender or you will all perish!*txt_ev6_bkg7_3~Soon the disease will render you powerless.*txt_ev6_bkg7_4~I will conquer the city and my master shall be very pleased.*txt_ev6_bkg7_5~All the city's inhabitants seem better. How is this possible?*txt_ev6_bkg12_1~My friend, the Healer, has gone to treat the city's inhabitants.*txt_ev6_bkg12_2~I know that she is missing mountain flowers to prepare her remedies.*txt_ev6_bkg12_3~The Healer has not returned from the city. The situation must be serious.*txt_ev6_bkg12_4~We must quickly gather purple mountain flowers to prepare the remedies.*txt_ev6_bkg12_5~I received news from the Healer. The epidemic seems to be eradicated.*txt_ev6_bkg24_1~The disease has spread quickly throughout the city.*txt_ev6_bkg24_2~I'm feeling worse than ever.*txt_ev6_bkg24_3~I feel a lot better. This remedy works like a charm.*txt_ev6_bkg25_1~Thank you young Spider Rider.*txt_ev6_bkg25_2~I will now prepare more remedies.*txt_ev6_bkg25_3~I have prepared a remedy for the disease.*txt_ev6_bkg25_4~But my reserves are low right now.*txt_ev6_bkg25_5~We need purple flowers from the mountain.*txt_ev6_bkg25_6~The worse is over now.*txt_ev6_bkg25_7~Thank you to all the Spider Riders for their precious help.*txt_ev6_bkg26_1~My parents are at home. They are caring for my very sick brother and sister.*txt_ev6_bkg26_2~My brothers and sisters are very sick.*txt_ev6_bkg26_3~And my mother is not well. She can't take care of them anymore.*txt_ev6_bkg26_4~My family is cured.*txt_ev6_bkg28_1~A mysterious epidemic is attacking the city.*txt_ev6_bkg28_2~We must help the Healer by bringing her purple flowers.*txt_ev6_bkg28_3~The only way to get them is to go to the mountain and to play a hunting game.*txt_ev6_bkg28_4~The Healer managed to contain the disease with her remedies.*txt_ev7_bkg8_1~Quickly, all the bundles must be picked up before the Invectids return and steal them.*txt_ev7_bkg8_2~I saw the Invectids approaching.*txt_ev7_bkg8_3~There isn't much time to gather the harvest.*txt_ev7_bkg8_4~We had enough help to finish all our harvesting.*txt_ev7_bkg12_1~Thank you. I will put them in the lofts to dry.*txt_ev7_bkg12_2~The lofts are ready to receive the harvest bundles.*txt_ev7_bkg12_3~The lofts are full now. It is a very good season.*txt_ev7_bkg13_1~We must finish harvesting before the Invectids return and attack us again.*txt_ev7_bkg13_2~We had enough help to finish all our harvesting.*txt_ev7_bkg16_1~We must bring the bundles to the shopkeeper.*txt_ev7_bkg16_2~I overheard the Invectids.*txt_ev7_bkg16_3~They want to steal our harvest.*txt_ev7_bkg16_4~Our harvest is safe.*txt_ev7_bkg26_1~It's harvest time in the village.*txt_ev7_bkg26_2~You know, with the help of our spiders, we could really give you a hand.*txt_ev7_bkg26_3~The bundles need to be transported to the shopkeeper.*txt_ev7_bkg26_4~The villagers have completed the harvest.*txt_ev7_bkg26_5~I heard that many Spider Riders had helped them.*txt_ev8_bkg24_1~From now on, this city belongs to us.*txt_ev8_bkg24_2~I must win this battle, for my master.*txt_ev8_bkg25_1~Never give up!*txt_ev8_bkg25_2~We're making headway.*txt_ev8_bkg25_3~We are victorious.*txt_ev8_bkg27_1~They must be defeated!*txt_ev8_bkg27_2~We have managed to resist them.*txt_ev8_bkg27_3~The city is saved.*txt_ev8_bkg28_1~Well done.*txt_ev8_bkg28_2~But it's not over. The counter-attack continues.*txt_ev8_bkg28_3~The city has been invaded!*txt_ev8_bkg28_4~I must know how many Invectids there are in order to prepare a counter-attack.*txt_ev8_bkg28_5~The counter-attack is working.*txt_ev8_bkg28_6~We have resisted Mantid's armies.*txt_ev8_bkg30_1~Mantid's troops are invading the city.*txt_ev8_bkg30_2~My brother is leading the counter-attack.*txt_ev8_bkg30_3~He needs your help.*txt_ev8_bkg30_4~Hail to all Spider Riders who battled to protect our city.*txt_ev9_bkg24_1~As soon as I finish my patrol, I'm going to the spider races.*txt_ev9_bkg24_2~There's still some time to go watch the championship spider races.*txt_ev9_bkg24_3~I love watching spider races.*txt_ev9_bkg26_1~I hear that racers from every region have come to participate in the championship.*txt_ev9_bkg26_2~Many racers broke track records.*txt_ev9_bkg26_3~The racers are leaving now that the championship is over.*txt_ev9_bkg27_1~The championship races have drawn a big crowd.*txt_ev9_bkg27_2~I wonder which Guild will win the championship.*txt_ev9_bkg27_3~The racing championship had a high calibre of competition this year.*txt_ev9_bkg28_1~There's a big spider racing championship.*txt_ev9_bkg28_2~Anyone can participate.*txt_ev9_bkg28_3~Winners are awarded stars that they must give to Prince Lumens.*txt_ev9_bkg28_4~Prince Lumens awarded a prize to the winning championship team.*txt_ev9_bkg30_1~Congratulations on your race.*txt_ev9_bkg30_2~We will find out who the big winners are in a few days.*txt_ev9_bkg30_3~I'm waiting for the race winners.*txt_ev9_bkg30_4~The championship is over.*txt_ev10_bkg7_1~My Guild will win this competition.*txt_ev10_bkg7_2~To all the members of my Guild: Give it all you've got! We must absolutely win.*txt_ev10_bkg22_1~I'm not worried about the Guild competition.*txt_ev10_bkg22_2~I know that my friends are the bravest.*txt_ev10_bkg22_3~I will be the one to win the statue.*txt_ev10_bkg22_4~There's little time left to win the Guild competition.*txt_ev10_bkg22_5~Be strong my friends.*txt_ev10_bkg25_1_1~My soldiers won't disappoint me.*txt_ev10_bkg25_1_2~This isn't the time to daydream. We need to collect more flags if we are going to win the tournament.*txt_ev10_bkg25_1_3~The match was a real success this year.*txt_ev10_bkg25_2_1~How strange it is to see yourself in stone.*txt_ev10_bkg25_3_1~This statue is beautiful.*txt_ev10_bkg26_1~Excellent. Your Guild will gain some points. Your perseverance is commendable.*txt_ev10_bkg26_2~In addition to my other responsibilities, I am responsible for the Guild Competition.*txt_ev10_bkg26_3~I must get back to my other matters.*txt_ev10_bkg28_1~It's an ancient tradition.*txt_ev10_bkg28_2~Every year, the Guilds compete with one another in a competition.*txt_ev10_bkg28_3~The goal is to find an object hidden in the regions of Arachna and to return it to the chamberlain.*txt_ev10_bkg28_4~The winning Guild wins a secret prize as well as a statue in honour of their leader.*txt_ev10_bkg28_5~The Guilds Match is over. Congratulations to all the participants.*txt_ev10_bkg30_1~I can't wait to find out which Guild will win the tournament this year.*txt_ev10_bkg30_2~It has been a most memorable tournament.*txt_ev11_bkg7_1~My little toy balls are hypnotizing the city's inhabitants.*txt_ev11_bkg7_2~It appears that my plan is unfolding perfectly.*txt_ev11_bkg7_3~What's happening? My toys should have returned with prisoners by now.*txt_ev11_bkg7_4~My plans have been foiled again. But I'll be back soon to destroy you.*txt_ev11_bkg24_1_1~I was in my room playing with my toy ball.*txt_ev11_bkg24_1_2~And suddenly, I woke up here. It's strange.*txt_ev11_bkg24_2_1~What happened?*txt_ev11_bkg25_1~Why aren't I at home?*txt_ev11_bkg26_1~I thought I was at my station. I must have fallen asleep.*txt_ev11_bkg27_1~That's funny. I was dreaming that I was flying, and all of a sudden, I woke up in the gardens.*txt_ev11_bkg28_1~You have succeeded in liberating the inhabitants.*txt_ev11_bkg28_2~Evil toys have possessed the city's inhabitants.*txt_ev11_bkg28_3~They must be liberated!*txt_ev11_bkg28_4~We must stop Grasshop's toys before they kidnap the city's inhabitants.*txt_ev11_bkg28_5~All the toys have been destroyed.*txt_ev11_bkg28_6~We were almost defeated this time.*txt_ev11_bkg28_7~But everyone is safe now.*txt_ev12_bkg7_1~Magma went patrolling in the marshes and hasn't returned yet.*txt_ev12_bkg7_2~I'm worried.*txt_ev12_bkg7_3~I think Magma is in trouble with Stag in the marshes.*txt_ev12_bkg7_4~Magma is on his way back.*txt_ev12_bkg15_1~Stag's prisoners were freed.*txt_ev12_bkg18_1~The school children have been captured by the Invectids.*txt_ev12_bkg18_2~I need some help.*txt_ev12_bkg18_3~Please, Spider Rider.*txt_ev12_bkg18_4~You must go the marshes and rescue the school children kidnapped by the Invectids.*txt_ev12_bkg18_5~I can hear the children's cries in the school.*txt_ev12_bkg18_6~I hope that they are well.*txt_ev12_bkg36_1~The school children have been made prisoners by Stag.*txt_ev12_bkg36_2~He won't release them until we vanquish his champion.*txt_ev12_bkg36_3~Attacking children... what a coward.*txt_ev12_bkg36_4~Stag is still holding more children.*txt_ev12_bkg36_5~But as time passes, our chances to rescue them are slimmer.*txt_ev12_bkg39_1_1~Help!!!*txt_ev12_bkg39_2_1~I will only release the prisoners if you can vanquish my champion.*txt_ev12_bkg39_2_2~This was truly a test of your courage.*txt_ev12_bkg39_3_1~Just try to vanquish our champion.*txt_ev12_bkg48_1_1~I was terribly scared of the Invectids.*txt_ev12_bkg48_2_1~You have found the children. Thank you so much!*txt_ev12_bkg48_2_2~The Invectids have captured the children of my school.*txt_ev12_bkg48_2_3~The children are safe and sound.*txt_ev12_bkg48_2_4~Thank you Spider Rider!</lockitworld>
<lockitbsystem>txt_en_wDoor~Wooden Door*txt_en_sDoor~Stone Door*txt_en_stat~Status*txt_en_for~Forest*txt_en_rock~Falling Rocks*txt_en_flow~Poisonous Flower*txt_en_spik~Spike*txt_en_expl~Explosion*txt_en_cBat~Cave Bat*txt_en_sTat~Small Nasty-Tat*txt_en_bTat~Big Nasty-Tat*txt_en_iLice~Ice lice*txt_en_aBee~Assisin Bee*txt_en_sWee~School of Weewogs*txt_en_sInv~Invectid soldier*txt_en_fInv~Flying Invectid*txt_en_coInv~Invectid Commander*txt_en_chInv~Invectid Champion*txt_en_wInv~Invectid Warrior*txt_en_dfInv~Dark Flying Invectid*txt_en_tInv~Invectid Trooper*txt_en_dInv~Invectid Driver*txt_en_sSoldier~Stag's Soldier*txt_en_gMons~Grasshop's Monster*txt_en_bMons~Buguese's Monster*txt_en_aMons~Aquine's Monster*txt_en_sCom~Scarab of combat*txtSpOppHand~Space for your opponent's hand*txtAttack~Your attack*txtOppAttack~Opponent's attack*txtOppDeck~Opponent's|deck*txtOppGrave~Opponent's|graveyard*txtDef~Your defense*txtOppDef~Opponent's defense*txtHand~Your hand*txtOppHand~Opponent's hand*txtThrow~Throw the dice*txtLaunchAtt~Launch attack*txtDrag~  Drag the dice onto cards|  of the same color to|  select them*txtRetreat~Retreat*txtDeck~Your|deck*txtGrave~Your|graveyard*txtYourHand~Space for your hand*txtHelpDetails~For more details, see the complete instructions|by clicking the "?" in the game interface.*txtSuccess~You were successful!*txtGet~You get*txtVicPts~Victory Points*btnRetreat~Are you sure you want to retreat?*btnRetreatCap~RETREAT*btnHelpCap~HELP*txtCounterCard~Select a card to counter*txtTutoMain1~To enter inside the temple and accomplish your mission, you must force open the door.*txtTutoMain2~To do that, you must overcome your|opponent's defenses by throwing|the dice.*txtTutoMain3~Your attack value is the basic|strength of your attack.*txtTutoMain4~It also indicates the number of dice|you can play for a better result.*txtTutoMain5~You can obtain five|possible results with|your dice.*txtTutoMain6~A red die gives|you an extra|attack point.*txtTutoMain7~A yellow die allows you to|play a yellow card that|causes more damage.*txtTutoMain8~A green die allows you to|play a green card that lets|you add equipment to|your character.*txtTutoMain9~A blue die allows you to play|a blue card to turn a situation|in your favor.*txtTutoMain10~To throw the dice,|click on the|"Throw the dice" button.*txtTutoMain11~To select a card, drag a dice|on a card of the same color.*txtTutoMain12~After dragging the dice on your cards,|click the "Launch Attack" button to|attack your opponent.*txtTutoDeck1~You now have more than|7 cards in your deck.*txtTutoDeck2~You will be dealt a new card at the|beginning of every turn until there are|no more cards left in your deck.*txtTutoDeck3~To use it,|drag it in your hand.*txtTutoDeck4~If all 7 spaces are used, discard one of|your cards in the trash bin to make|room for your new card.*txtNoMoreCards~Your opponent has no more cards to draw. You win the battle.*txtNoMoreCardsDraw~You have no more cards to draw. You have lost the battle.*txtMiss~miss*txtOops~Oops! There's no more card in your deck!*txtAlmostEmpty~Careful! Your deck is almost empty.*txtQuestRetreat~Do you really want to retreat ?</lockitbsystem>
<lockitchat>txtLoading~Loading...*txtPlayInvasion~Send an invite to play|THE INVASION*txtPlaySpiRaces~Send an invite to play|SPIDER RACES*txtPlayLumensResc~Send an invite to play|Lumen's RESCUE*txtPlayCardDuel~Send an invite to play|CARD DUEL*txtTrade~Send an invite to|TRADE CARDS</lockitchat>
<lockitmgames>txtBonus~BONUS FOR:|*txtDisconnect~DISCONNECTED*txtLeftToGo~left to go : *btnRestart~RESTART*btnPrev~PREVIOUS*btnNext~NEXT*txtMG1_Cleared~WAVE CLEARED*txtMG2_SelectSpi~SELECT YOUR SPIDER*txtMG2_Speed~speed*txtMG2_Stability~stability*txtMG2_SelectTrack~SELECT YOUR TRACK*txtMG2_TrckCity~City Cup*txtMG2_TrckForest~Dark Forest Cup*txtMG2_TrckPeak~Stony Peak Cup*txtMG2_Lap~Lap*txtMG2_Time~time*txtMG2_Energy~energy*txtMG2_Arachna~BACK TO ARACHNA*txtMG2_Lose~You lose*txtMG2_Win~You win!!*txtMG3_Seconds~Seconds*txtMG4_NotBad~Not Bad!*txtMG4_GJ~Good Job!!*txtMG4_Great~GREAT!!!*txtMG4_Photo~This photo| *txtMG4_TotPts~Total pts| *txtMG4_PhotoTop~Photo*txtMG4_PhotoLeft~Photos|left*txtMG4_PhotoTop~Photo*txtMG4_Finish~You have finished!*txtMG4_AllPhotos~All photos have been taken!*txtMG5_Boss~INCOMING BOS*txtMG5_S~S*txtMG5_Pts~ points*txtMG5_Health~ healths*txtMG5_Invincible~invincible 2 seconds*txtMG6Fr3_p1~Round score = 500|Health remaining = *txtMG6Fr3_p2~|Total Score = *txtMG6Fr3_p3~|Your current score = *txtMG6_Round~Round*txtMG6_Fight~FIGHT!</lockitmgames>
</setting>